<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<rdf:RDF
 xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#"
 xmlns="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/"
 xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
 xmlns:taxo="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/taxonomy/"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:syn="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
 xmlns:admin="http://webns.net/mvcb/"
>
<channel rdf:about="http://spotify.com/">
<title>Spotify new releases</title>
<link>http://spotify.com/</link>
<description rdf:parseType="Literal">Releases of followed artists on Spotify</description>
<dc:language>en-us</dc:language>
<dc:date>2018-03-07T20:30:00-05:00</dc:date>
<dc:publisher>help@spotify.com</dc:publisher>
<dc:subject>Music</dc:subject>
<syn:updateBase>1901-01-01T00:00+00:00</syn:updateBase>
<syn:updateFrequency>1</syn:updateFrequency>
<syn:updatePeriod>daily</syn:updatePeriod>
<items>
 <rdf:Seq>
<rdf:li rdf:resource="http://spotify.com"/></rdf:Seq>
</items>
<image rdf:resource="https://www.scdn.co/i/_global/favicon.png" />
</channel>
<image rdf:about="https://www.scdn.co/i/_global/favicon.png">
<title>Spotify releases</title>
<url>https://www.scdn.co/i/_global/favicon.png</url>
<link>http://spotify.com</link>
</image><item rdf:about="http://spotify.com">
<title>2021-03-29 07:46 Spotify newest releases</title>
<link>http://spotify.com</link>
<description rdf:parseType="Literal">&lt;p&gt;New releases:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maroon 5 - Red Pill Blues + (Deluxe)&lt;br&gt;Maroon 5 - Red Pill Blues (Deluxe)&lt;br&gt;Maroon 5 - Red Pill Blues (Deluxe)&lt;br&gt;Maroon 5 - Red Pill Blues (Deluxe)&lt;br&gt;Maroon 5 - Red Pill Blues (Deluxe)&lt;br&gt;Maroon 5 - Girls Like You (feat. Cardi B)&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - We Are Not Your Kind&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - Birth of the Cruel&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - Solway Firth / Unsainted&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - Unsainted&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - All Out Life&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - evermore&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - You All Over Me (feat. Maren Morris) (Taylor’s Version) (From The Vault)&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - Love Story (Taylor's Version) [Elvira Remix]&lt;br&gt;God Is An Astronaut - Ghost Tapes #10&lt;br&gt;God Is An Astronaut - Ghost Tapes #10&lt;br&gt;God Is An Astronaut - Epitaph&lt;br&gt;God Is An Astronaut - Epitaph&lt;br&gt;God Is An Astronaut - Fade&lt;br&gt;God Is An Astronaut - Fade&lt;br&gt;God Is An Astronaut - Burial&lt;br&gt;God Is An Astronaut - Burial&lt;br&gt;God Is An Astronaut - Komorebi&lt;br&gt;God Is An Astronaut - Komorebi&lt;br&gt;God Is An Astronaut - Epitaph&lt;br&gt;God Is An Astronaut - Epitaph&lt;br&gt;Serj Tankian - Elasticity&lt;br&gt;Serj Tankian - Elasticity&lt;br&gt;Serj Tankian - Black Blooms&lt;br&gt;Hollywood Undead - New Empire, Vol. 2&lt;br&gt;Hollywood Undead - New Empire, Vol. 1&lt;br&gt;Hollywood Undead - Gonna Be OK&lt;br&gt;Hollywood Undead - Heart Of A Champion (feat. Papa Roach & Ice Nine Kills)&lt;br&gt;Hollywood Undead - Coming Home + Idol (feat. Tech N9ne)&lt;br&gt;Hollywood Undead - Idol (feat. Tech N9ne)&lt;br&gt;Hollywood Undead - PSALMS&lt;br&gt;Hollywood Undead - Another Level&lt;br&gt;Hollywood Undead - Gotta Let Go&lt;br&gt;Hollywood Undead - Whatever It Takes (feat. Prodigal Sunn, Demrick and Fudd Rukus) [Mixtape]&lt;br&gt;Gojira - Amazonia&lt;br&gt;Volbeat - Rewind, Replay, Rebound&lt;br&gt;Ellie Goulding - Return to Love&lt;br&gt;Dirty Honey - Tied Up&lt;br&gt;Mötley Crüe - Looks That Kill (Live Pasadena '82)&lt;br&gt;Bonobo - Linked&lt;br&gt;Bonobo - Ibrik&lt;br&gt;Polaris - The Mortal Coil (Instrumental)&lt;br&gt;Polaris - The Death of Me&lt;br&gt;Polaris - The Death Of Me (Instrumental)&lt;br&gt;Polaris - Black Fingernails, Red Wine (triple j Like A Version)&lt;br&gt;Polaris - Landmine&lt;br&gt;Polaris - Hypermania&lt;br&gt;Polaris - Masochist&lt;br&gt;The Rumjacks - Hestia&lt;br&gt;The Rumjacks - Hestia&lt;br&gt;The Rumjacks - Live In Athens&lt;br&gt;The Rumjacks - Live in London - Acoustic Session&lt;br&gt;The Rumjacks - Saints Preserve Us&lt;br&gt;The Rumjacks - Good Night & Make Mends&lt;br&gt;The Rumjacks - Bullhead&lt;br&gt;The Rumjacks - Sainted Millions&lt;br&gt;The Rumjacks - Hestia&lt;br&gt;The Rumjacks - Cold London Rain&lt;br&gt;The Rumjacks - The Foreman O’Rourke&lt;br&gt;The Rumjacks - Bus Floor Bottles&lt;br&gt;The Rumjacks - Saints Preserve Us&lt;br&gt;CloZee - Evasion&lt;br&gt;CloZee - Zest Please&lt;br&gt;CloZee - ID (CloZee Remix)&lt;br&gt;CloZee - Evasion&lt;br&gt;Pantera - Live at Dynamo Open Air 1998&lt;br&gt;Clutch - The Weathermaker Vault Series, Vol. I&lt;br&gt;Clutch - Monsters, Machines, and Mythological Beasts&lt;br&gt;Clutch - Book of Bad Decisions&lt;br&gt;Clutch - Passive Restraints (The Weathermaker Vault Series)&lt;br&gt;Clutch - Run, John Barleycorn, Run (The Weathermaker Vault Series)&lt;br&gt;Clutch - Smoke Banshee (The Weathermaker Vault Series)&lt;br&gt;Clutch - Willie Nelson (The Weathermaker Vault Series)&lt;br&gt;Clutch - Spacegrass (The Weathermaker Vault Series)&lt;br&gt;Clutch - Fortunate Son (The Weathermaker Vault Series)&lt;br&gt;Clutch - Electric Worry (The Weathermaker Vault Series)&lt;br&gt;Clutch - Precious and Grace (The Weathermaker Vault Series)&lt;br&gt;Clutch - Evil (The Weathermaker Vault Series)&lt;br&gt;Clutch - In Walks Barbarella&lt;br&gt;Clutch - Hot Bottom Feeder&lt;br&gt;Clutch - How to Shake Hands&lt;br&gt;Clutch - Gimme the Keys&lt;br&gt;Oh Hiroshima - Oscillation&lt;br&gt;Oh Hiroshima - Oscillation&lt;br&gt;Oh Hiroshima - In Solar&lt;br&gt;Oh Hiroshima - In Solar&lt;br&gt;Oh Hiroshima - Moderate Spectre&lt;br&gt;Oh Hiroshima - Moderate Spectre&lt;br&gt;Oh Hiroshima - Darkroom Aesthetics&lt;br&gt;Oh Hiroshima - Darkroom Aesthetics&lt;br&gt;Tides From Nebula - From Voodoo to Zen&lt;br&gt;Tides From Nebula - Ghost Horses&lt;br&gt;Tides From Nebula - The New Delta&lt;br&gt;Tides From Nebula - Paratyphoid Fever&lt;br&gt;Tides From Nebula - Dopamine&lt;br&gt;Motörhead - Ace of Spades (40th Anniversary Edition;Deluxe)&lt;br&gt;Motörhead - Ace of Spades (40th Anniversary Master;Instrumental)&lt;br&gt;Motörhead - Shoot You in the Back (Live At Parc Expo, Orleans, 5th March 1981)&lt;br&gt;Motörhead - Ace of Spades (Live At Whitla Hall, Belfast 23rd December 1981)&lt;br&gt;Motörhead - Stay Clean (Live at Aylesbury Friars, 31st March 1979)&lt;br&gt;Motörhead - Bomber (Live in Le Mans 1979)&lt;br&gt;Motörhead - Overkill&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga - A Star Is Born Soundtrack&lt;br&gt;Bassnectar - Rabbit’s Revenge (feat. Bassnectar, Big Boi, and Killer Mike)&lt;br&gt;P!nk - Hurts 2B Human&lt;br&gt;Ghost - Prequelle&lt;br&gt;Ghost - Prequelle&lt;br&gt;Ghost - Seven Inches Of Satanic Panic&lt;br&gt;Ghost - Dance Macabre (Carpenter Brut Remix)&lt;br&gt;Ghost - Dance Macabre (Carpenter Brut Remix)&lt;br&gt;Prophets Of Rage - Pop Goes the Weapon&lt;br&gt;Prophets Of Rage - Made With Hate&lt;br&gt;Prophets Of Rage - Heart Afire&lt;br&gt;Christina Aguilera - Liberation&lt;br&gt;Pain of Salvation - The Perfect Element, Pt. 1 (Anniversary Mix 2020)&lt;br&gt;Pain of Salvation - PANTHER&lt;br&gt;Pain of Salvation - Used (Anniversary Mix 2020)&lt;br&gt;Pain of Salvation - Ashes (Anniversary Mix 2020)&lt;br&gt;Pain of Salvation - PANTHER&lt;br&gt;Pain of Salvation - RESTLESS BOY&lt;br&gt;Pain of Salvation - ACCELERATOR&lt;br&gt;TesseracT - Castles&lt;br&gt;TesseracT - Sonder&lt;br&gt;TesseracT - Sonder&lt;br&gt;TesseracT - ゾンダー&lt;br&gt;TesseracT - King&lt;br&gt;TesseracT - King&lt;br&gt;TesseracT - Luminary&lt;br&gt;TesseracT - Luminary&lt;br&gt;Knife Party - Battle Sirens (feat. Knife Party)&lt;br&gt;Nightwish - Decades (Remastered)&lt;br&gt;Myles Kennedy - Year Of The Tiger&lt;br&gt;Myles Kennedy - Year Of The Tiger&lt;br&gt;Myles Kennedy - The Ides of March&lt;br&gt;Myles Kennedy - The Ides Of March&lt;br&gt;Myles Kennedy - The Ides Of March&lt;br&gt;Myles Kennedy - In Stride&lt;br&gt;Myles Kennedy - In Stride&lt;br&gt;Myles Kennedy - Love Can Only Heal&lt;br&gt;Myles Kennedy - Love Can Only Heal&lt;br&gt;Myles Kennedy - Devil On The Wall&lt;br&gt;Myles Kennedy - Devil On The Wall&lt;br&gt;Myles Kennedy - Haunted By Design&lt;br&gt;Myles Kennedy - Haunted By Design&lt;br&gt;Dream Theater - Distant Memories - Live in London (Bonus Track Edition)&lt;br&gt;Dream Theater - Scene Three: II. Fatal Tragedy (Live at Hammersmith Apollo, London, UK, 2020)&lt;br&gt;Dream Theater - Pale Blue Dot (Live at Hammersmith Apollo, London, UK, 2020)&lt;br&gt;Wang Wen - 看不見的城市&lt;br&gt;Wang Wen - 大連,勿語&lt;br&gt;Wang Wen - 破曉&lt;br&gt;Wang Wen - 水之湄&lt;br&gt;Beats Antique - The Devil Dance&lt;br&gt;Killswitch Engage - Atonement&lt;br&gt;Killswitch Engage - I Can't Be the Only One (Alternate Edit)&lt;br&gt;Killswitch Engage - I Am Broken Too&lt;br&gt;Killswitch Engage - Unleashed&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Chronologic&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Chronologic&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Chronologic&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Chronologic&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Chronologic&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Chronologic&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Supersonics (Out Come the Freaks Edit)&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Supersonics (Out Come the Freaks Edit)&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Supersonics (Out Come the Freaks Edit)&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Supersonics (Out Come the Freaks Edit)&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Supersonics (Out Come the Freaks Edit)&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Supersonics (Out Come the Freaks Edit)&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Pluma&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Pluma&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Pluma&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Pluma&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Pluma&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Pluma&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Moonshine (Remixes)&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Moonshine&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Moonshine&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Moonshine&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Moonshine&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Moonshine&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Moonshine (Bakermat Remix)&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Moonshine (Bakermat Remix)&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Moonshine (Bakermat Remix)&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Moonshine (Bakermat Remix)&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Moonshine (Bakermat Remix)&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Moonshine (Bakermat Remix)&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Miracle&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Miracle&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Miracle (Remixes)&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Miracle (Remixes)&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Miracle (Remixes)&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Miracle&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Supersonics&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Supersonics&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Supersonics&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Supersonics&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Supersonics&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Plume&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Plume&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Plume&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Plume&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Plume&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Plume&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - About You&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - About You&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - About You&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - About You&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - About You&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - About You&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Miracle (Boogie Belgique Remix)&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Miracle (Boogie Belgique Remix)&lt;br&gt;Boogie Belgique - Miracle (Boogie Belgique Remix)&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Miracle (Boogie Belgique Remix)&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Miracle (Boogie Belgique Remix)&lt;br&gt;Boogie Belgique - Miracle (Boogie Belgique Remix) - Single&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Miracle&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Miracle&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Miracle&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Miracle&lt;br&gt;Caravan Palace - Miracle&lt;br&gt;While She Sleeps - SO WHAT?&lt;br&gt;While She Sleeps - You Are We (Special Edition)&lt;br&gt;While She Sleeps - You Are We (Special Edition)&lt;br&gt;While She Sleeps - You Are We (Special Edition)&lt;br&gt;While She Sleeps - FAKERS PLAGUE&lt;br&gt;While She Sleeps - ELEPHANT&lt;br&gt;While She Sleeps - THE GUILTY PARTY&lt;br&gt;While She Sleeps - HAUNT ME&lt;br&gt;While She Sleeps - Anti-Social&lt;br&gt;While She Sleeps - Silence Speaks (Alternative Version) [Live at St Pancras Church]&lt;br&gt;While She Sleeps - Silence Speaks (Alternative Version - Live at St Pancras Church)&lt;br&gt;While She Sleeps - Silence Speaks (Alternative Version - Live at St Pancras Church)&lt;br&gt;Gorillaz - Song Machine, Season One: Strange Timez (Deluxe)&lt;br&gt;Gorillaz - The Now Now&lt;br&gt;Gorillaz - Hollywood (feat. Snoop Dogg & Jamie Principle)&lt;br&gt;Baroness - Gold & Grey&lt;br&gt;Baroness - Gold & Grey&lt;br&gt;Baroness - Gold & Grey&lt;br&gt;Baroness - Live at Maida Vale BBC - Vol. II&lt;br&gt;Baroness - Live at Maida Vale BBC – Vol. II&lt;br&gt;Baroness - Throw Me An Anchor&lt;br&gt;Baroness - Seasons&lt;br&gt;Baroness - Borderlines&lt;br&gt;Long Distance Calling - How Do We Want to Live?&lt;br&gt;Long Distance Calling - Immunity&lt;br&gt;Long Distance Calling - Voices&lt;br&gt;Long Distance Calling - Hazard&lt;br&gt;Meshuggah - The Violent Sleep Of Reason (Japan Edition)&lt;br&gt;Meshuggah - Koloss (Japan Edition)&lt;br&gt;Meshuggah - Catch ThirtyThree (Japan Edition)&lt;br&gt;Meshuggah - Nothing (Japan Edition)&lt;br&gt;Meshuggah - Chaosphere (Japan Edition)&lt;br&gt;Meshuggah - Destroy Erase Improve (Japan Edition)&lt;br&gt;Meshuggah - Contradictions Collapse (Japan Edition)&lt;br&gt;Skindred - Big Tings&lt;br&gt;Skindred - Big Tings&lt;br&gt;Skindred - Big Tings&lt;br&gt;Skindred - That's My Jam&lt;br&gt;Skindred - That's My Jam&lt;br&gt;Skindred - Big Tings&lt;br&gt;Skindred - Big Tings&lt;br&gt;Skindred - Machine (Radio Edit)&lt;br&gt;Skindred - Machine (Radio Edit)&lt;br&gt;Hollywood Vampires - Rise&lt;br&gt;Hollywood Vampires - Rise&lt;br&gt;Hollywood Vampires - Rise&lt;br&gt;Hollywood Vampires - Rise&lt;br&gt;Hollywood Vampires - Heroes&lt;br&gt;Hollywood Vampires - Heroes&lt;br&gt;Hollywood Vampires - Heroes&lt;br&gt;Hollywood Vampires - The Boogieman Surprise&lt;br&gt;Hollywood Vampires - The Boogieman Surprise&lt;br&gt;Hollywood Vampires - The Boogieman Surprise&lt;br&gt;Hollywood Vampires - Who's Laughing Now&lt;br&gt;Hollywood Vampires - Who's Laughing Now&lt;br&gt;Hollywood Vampires - Who's Laughing Now&lt;br&gt;Sabaton - The Great War&lt;br&gt;Sabaton - The Great War (History Edition)&lt;br&gt;Sabaton - Soundtrack To The Great War&lt;br&gt;Sabaton - Great War&lt;br&gt;Sabaton - The Red Baron&lt;br&gt;Wolfmother - Chase The Feeling (feat. Chris Cester (Jet))&lt;br&gt;Wolfmother - Joker & The Thief (Final Hour Mix)&lt;br&gt;Tremonti - A Dying Machine&lt;br&gt;Tremonti - A Dying Machine (Deluxe Version)&lt;br&gt;Tremonti - A Dying Machine (Deluxe Version)&lt;br&gt;Tremonti - As The Silence Becomes Me&lt;br&gt;Tremonti - As The Silence Becomes Me&lt;br&gt;Tremonti - Bringer Of War&lt;br&gt;Tremonti - Bringer Of War&lt;br&gt;Tremonti - Take You With Me&lt;br&gt;Tremonti - Take You With Me&lt;br&gt;Tremonti - A Dying Machine&lt;br&gt;Tremonti - A Dying Machine&lt;br&gt;Stone Sour - Hello, You Bastards: Live in Reno&lt;br&gt;Stone Sour - Hello, You Bastards: Live In Reno&lt;br&gt;Stone Sour - Whiplash Pants (Live)&lt;br&gt;Stone Sour - Whiplash Pants (Live)&lt;br&gt;Stone Sour - Absolute Zero - Live&lt;br&gt;Stone Sour - Absolute Zero&lt;br&gt;Slash - Conspiracy Series Volume1&lt;br&gt;Slash - Living The Dream&lt;br&gt;Slash - Living the Dream&lt;br&gt;Slash - Living the Dream (feat. Myles Kennedy and The Conspirators)&lt;br&gt;Slash - My Antidote (feat. Myles Kennedy and The Conspirators)&lt;br&gt;Slash - My Antidote / Mind Your Manners / Driving Rain (feat. Myles Kennedy and The Conspirators)&lt;br&gt;Slash - Mind Your Manners&lt;br&gt;Slash - Mind Your Manners (feat. Myles Kennedy and The Conspirators)&lt;br&gt;Slash - Mind Your Manners / Driving Rain (feat. Myles Kennedy and The Conspirators)&lt;br&gt;Slash - Driving Rain (feat. Myles Kennedy and The Conspirators)&lt;br&gt;Slash - Driving Rain (feat. Myles Kennedy and The Conspirators)&lt;br&gt;A Perfect Circle - Eat The Elephant&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge - Walk The Sky 2.0 (Deluxe)&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge - Walk The Sky&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge - Walk The Sky&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge - Walk The Sky 2.0 (Deluxe)&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge - Live At The Royal Albert Hall&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge - Live At The Royal Albert Hall (feat. The Parallax Orchestra)&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge - Last Rites&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge - Last Rites&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge - Native Son (Live)&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge - Native Son (Live)&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge - Native Son&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge - Native Son&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge - The End Is Here (Live At The Royal Albert Hall)&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge - Words Darker Than Their Wings (Live At The Royal Albert Hall)&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge - Addicted To Pain (Live At The Royal Albert Hall)&lt;br&gt;Cypress Hill - Elephants on Acid&lt;br&gt;Cypress Hill - Champion Sound&lt;br&gt;Cypress Hill - Champion Sound&lt;br&gt;Cypress Hill - Locos&lt;br&gt;Cypress Hill - Crazy&lt;br&gt;Cypress Hill - Muggs Is Dead&lt;br&gt;Cypress Hill - Band of Gypsies (Edit)&lt;br&gt;Enduser - Crash Report (Enduser Remix)&lt;br&gt;Boogie Belgique - Prelude to Machine&lt;br&gt;Love and Death - Perfectly Preserved&lt;br&gt;Love and Death - The Hunter&lt;br&gt;Love and Death - White Flag&lt;br&gt;Love and Death - Down&lt;br&gt;Daft Punk - I Gotta Try You Girl (Daft Punk Edit)&lt;br&gt;In Flames - アイ、ザ・マスク&lt;br&gt;In Flames - I, The Mask&lt;br&gt;In Flames - Burn&lt;br&gt;In Flames - I, The Mask&lt;br&gt;In Flames - (This Is Our) House&lt;br&gt;In Flames - I Am Above&lt;br&gt;In Flames - Down, Wicked & No Good&lt;br&gt;Excision - Apex&lt;br&gt;Excision - Breaking Through&lt;br&gt;Saliva - Your Disease (2021 Version)&lt;br&gt;Skrillex - Goh (feat. KLP)&lt;br&gt;Skrillex - Goh&lt;br&gt;Skrillex - Goh&lt;br&gt;Tycho - Weather Remixes&lt;br&gt;Tycho - Simulcast&lt;br&gt;Tycho - Weather&lt;br&gt;Tycho - Weather&lt;br&gt;Tycho - Epoch (Deluxe Version)&lt;br&gt;Tycho - No Stress (Com Truise Remix)&lt;br&gt;Tycho - Weather (Nitemoves Remix)&lt;br&gt;Tycho - Into The Woods (Christopher Willits Remix)&lt;br&gt;Tycho - For How Long (Harvey Sutherland Remix)&lt;br&gt;Tycho - Easy (Mild Minds Remix)&lt;br&gt;Tycho - Japan (Satin Jackets Remix)&lt;br&gt;Tycho - Run Away&lt;br&gt;Tycho - Outer Sunset&lt;br&gt;Tycho - Stress&lt;br&gt;Tycho - Skate (pluko Remix)&lt;br&gt;Tycho - Pink & Blue (RAC Mix)&lt;br&gt;Tycho - Japan&lt;br&gt;Tycho - Japan&lt;br&gt;Tycho - Pink & Blue&lt;br&gt;Tycho - Pink & Blue&lt;br&gt;Tycho - Easy&lt;br&gt;Tycho - Easy&lt;br&gt;Tycho - Epoch (Luttrell Remix)&lt;br&gt;Tycho - Horizon (Poolside Remix)&lt;br&gt;Five Finger Death Punch - A Decade of Destruction, Vol.2&lt;br&gt;Five Finger Death Punch - A Decade of Destruction, Vol.2&lt;br&gt;Five Finger Death Punch - And Justice for None (Deluxe)&lt;br&gt;Five Finger Death Punch - And Justice for None (Deluxe)&lt;br&gt;Five Finger Death Punch - And Justice for None&lt;br&gt;Five Finger Death Punch - Wrong Side of Heaven (Acoustic)&lt;br&gt;Five Finger Death Punch - Blue on Black (Outlaws Remix)&lt;br&gt;Five Finger Death Punch - Blue on Black&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea - Survive The Summer&lt;br&gt;BABYMETAL - 10 BABYMETAL YEARS&lt;br&gt;BABYMETAL - LEGEND – METAL GALAXY [DAY 2]&lt;br&gt;BABYMETAL - LEGEND – METAL GALAXY [DAY 1]&lt;br&gt;BABYMETAL - LEGEND - METAL GALAXY [DAY-2] (METAL GALAXY WORLD TOUR IN JAPAN EXTRA SHOW)&lt;br&gt;BABYMETAL - LEGEND - METAL GALAXY [DAY-1] (METAL GALAXY WORLD TOUR IN JAPAN EXTRA SHOW)&lt;br&gt;BABYMETAL - METAL GALAXY&lt;br&gt;BABYMETAL - METAL GALAXY&lt;br&gt;BABYMETAL - METAL GALAXY&lt;br&gt;BABYMETAL - Metal Galaxy&lt;br&gt;BABYMETAL - From Dusk Till Dawn&lt;br&gt;BABYMETAL - BxMxC&lt;br&gt;BABYMETAL - Brand New Day - METAL GALAXY WORLD TOUR IN JAPAN EXTRA SHOW&lt;br&gt;BABYMETAL - Headbangeeeeerrrrr!!!!! - METAL GALAXY WORLD TOUR IN JAPAN EXTRA SHOW&lt;br&gt;BABYMETAL - Shanti Shanti Shanti / Elevator Girl (English Version) / Pa Pa Ya!! / Starlight&lt;br&gt;BABYMETAL - Shanti Shanti Shanti&lt;br&gt;BABYMETAL - Shanti Shanti Shanti / Elevator Girl (English Version) / PA PA YA!! / Starlight&lt;br&gt;BABYMETAL - Elevator Girl (English Version) / Pa Pa Ya!! / Starlight&lt;br&gt;BABYMETAL - Elevator Girl (English Version) / PA PA YA!! / Starlight&lt;br&gt;BABYMETAL - PA PA YA!! (feat. F.HERO)&lt;br&gt;BABYMETAL - Elevator Girl&lt;br&gt;BABYMETAL - Starlight&lt;br&gt;BABYMETAL - Distortion&lt;br&gt;BABYMETAL - Distortion&lt;br&gt;Alice In Chains - Rainier Fog&lt;br&gt;Alice In Chains - Never Fade&lt;br&gt;Alice In Chains - So Far Under&lt;br&gt;Alice In Chains - The One You Know&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande - Sweetener&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande - thank u, next&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande - boyfriend&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande - MONOPOLY&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande - 7 rings (Remix)&lt;br&gt;Rise Against - Broken Dreams, Inc.&lt;br&gt;Godsmack - When Legends Rise&lt;br&gt;Godsmack - When Legends Rise&lt;br&gt;Godsmack - Bulletproof&lt;br&gt;Otep - Kult 45&lt;br&gt;Otep - KULT 45&lt;br&gt;Otep - Molotov&lt;br&gt;Otep - Molotov&lt;br&gt;Otep - Shelter In Place&lt;br&gt;Otep - Shelter In Place&lt;br&gt;Otep - To The Gallows&lt;br&gt;Otep - To The Gallows&lt;br&gt;Walk Off the Earth - HERE WE GO!&lt;br&gt;Walk Off the Earth - How it is&lt;br&gt;Walk Off the Earth - A Few Good Stories&lt;br&gt;Walk Off the Earth - this is love&lt;br&gt;Walk Off the Earth - Farther We Go (A Capella)&lt;br&gt;Walk Off the Earth - Farther We Go&lt;br&gt;Walk Off the Earth - Oh What a Feeling&lt;br&gt;Walk Off the Earth - Nicknames (feat. gnash)&lt;br&gt;Walk Off the Earth - I'll Be There (Kokaholla Remix)&lt;br&gt;Walk Off the Earth - I'll Be There (Liquid Todd Remix)&lt;br&gt;Walk Off the Earth - Home Alone&lt;br&gt;Walk Off the Earth - I'll Be There&lt;br&gt;Walk Off the Earth - Mike's Song&lt;br&gt;Iron Maiden - Nights of the Dead, Legacy of the Beast: Live in Mexico City&lt;br&gt;Iron Maiden - Sign of the Cross (Live in Mexico City, Palacio de los Deportes, Mexico, September 2019)&lt;br&gt;Iron Maiden - Aces High (Live in Mexico City, Palacio de los Deportes, Mexico, September 2019)&lt;br&gt;Halestorm - Vicious&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish - Lo Vas A Olvidar (with ROSALÍA)&lt;br&gt;Mike Shinoda - Grand Paradise (Mike Shinoda Mix)&lt;br&gt;Mike Shinoda - About You (feat. blackbear)&lt;br&gt;Mike Shinoda - Post Traumatic EP&lt;br&gt;Danko Jones - A Rock Supreme&lt;br&gt;Danko Jones - A Rock Supreme&lt;br&gt;Danko Jones - A Rock Supreme&lt;br&gt;Danko Jones - A Rock Supreme&lt;br&gt;Danko Jones - I Want Out&lt;br&gt;Danko Jones - I Want Out&lt;br&gt;Danko Jones - Fists up High&lt;br&gt;Danko Jones - Fists up High&lt;br&gt;Danko Jones - Fists Up High&lt;br&gt;Danko Jones - Fists up High&lt;br&gt;Danko Jones - Lipstick City&lt;br&gt;Danko Jones - Lipstick City&lt;br&gt;Danko Jones - Lipstick City&lt;br&gt;Danko Jones - Lipstick City&lt;br&gt;Danko Jones - I'm in a Band&lt;br&gt;Danko Jones - I'm in a Band&lt;br&gt;Danko Jones - I'm in a Band&lt;br&gt;Danko Jones - I'm In A Band&lt;br&gt;Danko Jones - Dance Dance Dance&lt;br&gt;Danko Jones - Dance Dance Dance&lt;br&gt;Danko Jones - Dance Dance Dance&lt;br&gt;Danko Jones - Dance Dance Dance&lt;br&gt;Danko Jones - Burn in Hell&lt;br&gt;Danko Jones - Burn In Hell&lt;br&gt;Danko Jones - Burn in Hell&lt;br&gt;Danko Jones - Burn in Hell&lt;br&gt;Danko Jones - We're Crazy&lt;br&gt;Danko Jones - We're Crazy&lt;br&gt;Danko Jones - We're Crazy&lt;br&gt;Danko Jones - We're Crazy&lt;br&gt;Arctic Monkeys - Tranquility Base Hotel & Casino&lt;br&gt;Arctic Monkeys - Tranquility Base Hotel & Casino&lt;br&gt;Arctic Monkeys - Tranquility Base Hotel & Casino&lt;br&gt;Arctic Monkeys - Spotify Singles&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys - Brothers (Deluxe Remastered Anniversary Edition)&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys - The Black Keys the Early Years&lt;br&gt;Lil Jon - OXY&lt;br&gt;Lil Jon - Oxy&lt;br&gt;Lil Jon - Oxy&lt;br&gt;Lil Jon - OXY&lt;br&gt;Lil Jon - Ain't No Tellin' (with Mac Dre)&lt;br&gt;Lil Jon - Beast&lt;br&gt;Lil Jon - Alive&lt;br&gt;Lil Jon - Alive (with Offset & 2 Chainz)&lt;br&gt;Dropkick Murphys - Middle Finger&lt;br&gt;Dropkick Murphys - Christmas (Baby Please Come Home)&lt;br&gt;Dropkick Murphys - Mick Jones Nicked My Pudding&lt;br&gt;Dropkick Murphys - Smash Shit Up
&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
<dc:creator> &lt;a&gt;Bednar&lt;/a&gt;</dc:creator>
</item>
</rdf:RDF>