<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<rdf:RDF
 xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#"
 xmlns="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/"
 xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
 xmlns:taxo="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/taxonomy/"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:syn="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
 xmlns:admin="http://webns.net/mvcb/"
>
<channel rdf:about="http://spotify.com/">
<title>Spotify new releases</title>
<link>http://spotify.com/</link>
<description rdf:parseType="Literal">Releases of followed artists on Spotify</description>
<dc:language>en-us</dc:language>
<dc:date>2018-03-07T20:30:00-05:00</dc:date>
<dc:publisher>help@spotify.com</dc:publisher>
<dc:subject>Music</dc:subject>
<syn:updateBase>1901-01-01T00:00+00:00</syn:updateBase>
<syn:updateFrequency>1</syn:updateFrequency>
<syn:updatePeriod>daily</syn:updatePeriod>
<items>
 <rdf:Seq>
<rdf:li rdf:resource="http://spotify.com"/></rdf:Seq>
</items>
<image rdf:resource="https://www.scdn.co/i/_global/favicon.png" />
</channel>
<image rdf:about="https://www.scdn.co/i/_global/favicon.png">
<title>Spotify releases</title>
<url>https://www.scdn.co/i/_global/favicon.png</url>
<link>http://spotify.com</link>
</image><item rdf:about="http://spotify.com">
<title>2020-07-12 09:51 YouTube newest rejects</title>
<link>http://spotify.com</link>
<description rdf:parseType="Literal">&lt;p&gt;New releases:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - Unsainted (Behind The Scenes) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Behind the scenes.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - Pollution - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - Nero Forte [OFFICIAL VIDEO] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - Europe AND UK 2020 Tour Announce - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Alexa: Play 'We Are Not Your Kind' by Slipknot (Amazon Music) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - Insert Coin (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - Death Because of Death (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - Red Flag (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - Not Long For This World (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - Critical Darling (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - Spiders (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - My Pain (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - Orphan (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - A Liar's Funeral (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - What's Next (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - Cornelia Street (Live From Paris) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Live.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - Death By A Thousand Cuts (Live From Paris) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Live.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - The Archer (Live From Paris) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Live.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - Daylight (Live From Paris) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Live.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - ME! (Live From Paris) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Live.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - You Need To Calm Down (Live From Paris) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Live.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - Lover (Live From Paris) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Live.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - Cornelia Street (Live From Paris) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Live.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - The Man (Behind The Scenes: The Umpire) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - The Man (Behind The Scenes: Directing) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - The Man (Behind The Scenes: Becoming The Man) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - The Man (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - The Man (Live From Paris) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - The Man (Lyric Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - Only The Young (Featured in Miss Americana / Lyric Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rebel Wizard - raiseth up all those that be bowed down - Contained not followed artist.
&lt;br&gt;RoyalRepublic - We Are The Royal Special - Live Stream from KB | #StayHome and DANCE #WithMe - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic - Anna-Leigh (Club Majesty Live@Rockpalast) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic - Fireman AND Dancer (Club Majesty Live@Rockpalast) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic - Getting Along (Club Majesty Live@Rockpalast) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic - Baby (Club Majesty Live@Rockpalast) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic feat. Ralf Gyllenhammar - Double Nature (Club Majesty Live@Stockholm) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic - Club Majesty Tour 2019/2020 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic - Stop Movin' (Club Majesy Live@Skärgårdsfest) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic - What a summer! Can't wait to kick off the Club Majesty European Tour in October! - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic - Like A Lover (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic - Anna-Leigh (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic - Boomerang (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic - Fireman AND Dancer (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic Tour Postmonement 2019 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic 10 Years Anniversary Movie (Part 6) - Highlights - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Gojira at Red Rocks - PRAY (extended version) LIVE - Contained GENERIC phrase: Live.
&lt;br&gt;Mario Duplantier - Drum solo Bloodstock 2018 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;GOJIRA - Pol'And'Rock Festival 2018 [LIVE] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;GOJIRA - Bloodstock 2018 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;GOJIRA - Into The Grave Festival 2018 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;GOJIRA - Brutal Assault 2018 (Czech Republic) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Gojira - Lokerse Feesten (Belgium) 2018 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;GOJIRA - Wacken Open Air 2018 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;GOJIRA - POL'AND ROCK 2018 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Gojira - Global Warming [Live at the Silver Cord Studio May 2018] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;GOJIRA - Silvera live - Hellfest 2016 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Gojira - Toxic Garbage Island ( Live Hellfest 2016) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;THE MAGMA TOUR US - Fall 2017 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Magma Tour - US October 2017 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Gojira - North America - August 2017 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Post Malone AND Red Hot Chili Peppers - Stay / Rockstar / Dark Necessities (LIVE at the 61st GRAMMYs) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Flea On RHCP Fans [The Getaway Track-By-Track Commentary] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Flea On His Preshow Rituals  [The Getaway Track-By-Track Commentary] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Goodbye Angels [OFFICIAL VIDEO] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Chad On His Preshow Rituals [The Getaway Track-By-Track Commentary] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Flea on Free Time Between Albums [The Getaway Track-By-Track Commentary] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Anthony on Relationship with Fans [The Getaway Track-By-Track Commentary] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Josh's Preshow Rituals [The Getaway Track-By-Track Commentary] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Anthony On Working With Brian Burton [The Getaway Track-By-Track Commentary] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Anthony's Preshow Rituals [The Getaway Track-By-Track Commentary] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Sick Love [OFFICIAL VIDEO] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Anthony Explains the Album Title [The Getaway Track-By-Track Commentary] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Flea on the Energy of the Live Shows [The Getaway Track-By-Track Commentary] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - The Getaway [Live Download from Munich, Germany 11.01.16] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Nobody Weird Like Me [Live Download from Munich, Germany 11.01.16] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;SPLID: The Album - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak- Rogaland Live at Lindmo - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak: Recording SPLID (Part 2) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak: Recording SPLID (Part 1) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak - Bronsegud [OFFICIAL VIDEO] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak - Svartmesse [OFFICIAL VIDEO] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak - Nattesferd [OFFICIAL VIDEO] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak - Heksebrann (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak - Berserkr (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak - Dendrofil for Yggdrasil (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak - Ondskapens Galakse (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak - Nekrodamus (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak - Svartmesse (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak - Nattesferd (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak - 1985 [OFFICIAL VIDEO] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ellie Goulding - Power (Live from TIME100 Talks) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Live.
&lt;br&gt;Ellie Goulding - Flux (Live from TIME100 Talks) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Live.
&lt;br&gt;Ellie Goulding - Slow Grenade (Lyric Video) ft. Lauv - Contained GENERIC phrase: Lyric Video.
&lt;br&gt;Worry About Me (Live On "The Late Late Show With James Corden", Hollywood / 2020) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ellie Goulding - Worry About Me (Live On "Jimmy Kimmel Live!", Hollywood / 2020) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ellie Goulding, blackbear - Worry About Me (Director's Cut) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ellie Goulding - Burn (Live at Coachella 2016) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ellie Goulding - Worry About Me (feat. blackbear) [Behind The Scenes] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Workout with Ellie Goulding AND Joe Wicks aka TheBodyCoach - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ellie Goulding, blackbear - Worry About Me (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ellie Goulding - River (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ellie Goulding kicks off Dallas Cowboys half time show in aid of Salvation Army Red Kettle Campaign - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ellie Goulding - River [Amazon Original] (Behind The Scenes) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Greatest Story is Now - Ellie Goulding - OYW 2019 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit - Toazted Interview 1998 (part 2) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit - Toazted Interview 1998 (part 1) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit - Toazted Interview 1998 (part 3) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit - Toazted Interview 1998 (part 4) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Endless Slaughter (Official Visual 2014) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;LIGHTZ (Official Video) - Limp Bizkit - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit "Behind Blue Eyes" - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit "Boiler" - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit "Break Stuff" - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit "Eat You Alive" - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit "My Way" - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit "Faith" REMIX - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit - Ready To Go (Official Music Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit - Lightz - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit - Ready To Go ft. Lil Wayne (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ahmed ag Kaedy and Embryo - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Embryo live February 2017 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Embryo feat. Deobrat and Prashant Mishra 2017 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Embryo - Mal Waldron -  Memorial Concert - Left Alone - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Embryo in the Seventies, Vlotho 78 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Embryo in the Seventies, Feature, WDR 1980 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Embryo and Friends, La Pirata, Llanca, Spain, 21.02.2016 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Embryo + Wieland Rehm - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Embryo live, Embryokeller München 09.Januar 2016 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Embryo and Mal Waldron, TU Mensa Munich,  29. Nov. 1990 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;ADM - Free-Haven - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mal Waldron AND Embryo, 20 Jahrfeier, Part I - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mal Waldron AND Embryo, 20 Jahrfeier, Part II - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Embryo - Agnessession - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Roman Bunka AND Christian Burchard - Sunsong - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - The Making of Crack The Skye | Part 6 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - Stairway to Heaven [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - Stairway to Heaven (Live) [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - The Making of Crack The Skye | Part 5 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - The Making of Crack The Skye | Part 4 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - The Making of Crack The Skye | Part 3 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - The Making of Crack The Skye | Part 2 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - Ghost of Karelia [Official Visualizer] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - Divinations [Official Visualizer] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - The Last Baron [Official Visualizer] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - Quintessence [Official Visualizer] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - Crack The Skye [Official Visualizer] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - The Czar [Official Visualizer] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - Oblivion [Official Visualizer] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - The Making of Crack The Skye | Part 1 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga, BLACKPINK - Sour Candy (Lyric Video) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Lyric Video.
&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga - Chromatica III (Audio) - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga - Babylon (Audio) - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga - Fun Tonight (Audio) - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga - Replay (Audio) - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga - 1000 Doves (Audio) - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga - Alice (Audio) - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga - Free Woman (Audio) - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga, Elton John - Sine From Above (Audio) - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga - Plastic Doll (Audio) - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga - Enigma (Audio) - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga - Chromatica II (Audio) - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga - Chromatica I (Audio) - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga - 911 (Audio) - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - Hurts 2B Human (Kat Krazy Remix (Audio)) ft. Khalid - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - Hurts 2B Human (FTampa Remix (Audio)) ft. Khalid - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - Hurts 2B Human (Alex Ghenea Remix (Audio)) ft. Khalid - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - Hurts 2B Human (Midnight Kids Remix (Audio)) ft. Khalid - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - Hurts 2B Human (Frank Pole Remix (Audio)) ft. Khalid - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - Hurts 2B Human feat. Khalid - Behind The Scenes - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - Hurts 2B Human ft. Khalid - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - Can We Pretend (Animated Video) ft. Cash Cash - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - Can We Pretend (Sigala Remix (Audio)) ft. Cash Cash - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - 90 Days (Official Video) ft. Wrabel - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - Walk Me Home (Dinaire+Bissen Remix (Audio)) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - Walk Me Home (R3HAB Extended Mix (Audio)) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - Walk Me Home (Until Dawn Remix (Audio)) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;P!nk VS Sink The Pink in Walk Me Home - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - Circle Game (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Przegryw z Kazonem (Nocny Kochanek) - Wódżitsu S01E01 (PLAYTHROUGH) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;NOCNY KOCHANEK - Alkustycznie (koncert) (2020) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Nocny Kochanek - Andżeju (Alkustycznie) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Let's Bash | The Unauthorized Bash Brothers Experience - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Alexa, play me some hot garbage (this actually works) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Uniform On | The Unauthorized Bash Brothers Experience - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Oakland Nights (feat. Sia) | The Unauthorized Bash Brothers Experience - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Lil' Tour Announcement - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;OSCAR SONG DEMO - "Why Not Me?" - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Jack Sparrow Unplugged (from Michael Bolton's Netflix Special) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Old Time Rock N Roll (from Netflix's Michael Bolton's Big Sexy Valentine's Day Special) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Natalie's Rap 2.0 (Uncensored Version) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;I'm On A Boat - Classroom Instruments w Jimmy Fallon AND The Roots - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Shy Ronnie (ft. Rihanna) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;conner4real Radio Freestyle - Big Boy (92.3) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Lazy Sunday Live w/ The Roots - Late Night w Jimmy Fallon - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;conner4real - "F**k Off" (Popstar Deleted Scene/Song) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Christina Aguilera, A Great Big World - Fall On Me - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;A Great Big World AND Christina Aguilera - Fall On Me (Live from the 2019 AMAs) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Christina Aguilera - Haunted Heart (Lyric Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Christina Aguilera: The Xperience - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Christina Aguilera - Like I Do (Lyric Video) ft. GoldLink - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Christina Aguilera - Fall In Line feat. Demi Lovato - Behind The Scenes - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Christina Aguilera - Like I Do (Audio) ft. GoldLink - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Christina Aguilera - Fall In Line (Official Video) ft. Demi Lovato - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Christina Aguilera ft. Demi Lovato - Fall In Line (Official Lyric Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Christina Aguilera - Twice (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Where’s Maria? (Liberation by Christina Aguilera) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Christina Aguilera - Accelerate (Official Video) ft. Ty Dolla $ign, 2 Chainz - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Christina Aguilera - Ven Conmigo (Solamente Tú) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Christina Aguilera - Telepathy (feat. Nile Rodgers) [Fan Video] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine - Kamuflaże 🍷 (Quarantine Edition) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine - Znak 🔑 (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Przebój Rocku Antyradia - "Jak Ci Powiedzieć?"🎸 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine - Błyski ⚡ (Lyric Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine - Jak Ci Powiedzieć? 🎱 (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine - Odchodząc 🏁 (Republika Cover) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine - Pretending 🔮 (Official Live Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine - Neverland 🍂 (Official Live Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine - Secret Self 🎭 (Live ❣ WOŚP ❣ Sanok) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine - Dicegame 🎲(Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine - Broken 🖤 (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine - Stop Me💸(Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine - Secret Self 🎭(Acoustic Czwórka) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine #Stop Me (Trailer) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;RAU_PERFORMANCE #HOT16CHALLENGE2 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;RAU_PERFORMANCE - NIECH MNIE KTOS USZCZYPNIE - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;TECHNOTORIOUS R.A.U. - ROLEX WATCHES - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;PŁOMIEŃ 81 - POWIEDZ NA OSIEDLU – INTERPRETACJE / zapowiedź - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Proseko - Wsiadam do auta (prod. megot) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;RAU_PERFORMANCE - ODKRYJ W SOBIE LATO. - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;RAU_PERFORMANCE - FYI (INTRO) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;RAU_PERFORMANCE - NIKT W POLSCE. - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;RAU_PERFORMANCE - ŚCIANA - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;RAU_PERFORMANCE - DOJADAMY (FT. KSIĄŻE KAPOTA, FROSTI REGE, ŻYTO) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;RAU_PERFORMANCE - MISTRZ_SZTUKI. - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;EN2AK FT. RAU - GUMOWA KACZKA [POLAKPOTRAFI.PL] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;RAU_PERFORMANCE - NIE DZWOŃ, NIE PISZ. - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;🍄 ŚMIESZNY GRZYB 🍄 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;BAASCH - KIND OF COMA (RAU REMIX) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Marilyn Manson - Personal Jesus (Live) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Marilyn Manson - God's Gonna Cut You Down (Official Music Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Marilyn Manson - Cry Little Sister - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Marilyn Manson - Cry Little Sister - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Marilyn Manson AND Rob Zombie Discuss The First Time They Heard Each Other's Music - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Twins of Evil Tour – The Second Coming - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Marilyn Manson - Tattooed In Reverse (Music Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Marilyn Manson - KILL4ME (Music Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;MARILYN MANSON - Revelation #12 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;MARILYN MANSON - Tattooed In Reverse - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;MARILYN MANSON - Saturnalia - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;MARILYN MANSON - JE$U$ CRI$I$ - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;MARILYN MANSON - Blood Honey - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;MARILYN MANSON - Heaven Upside Down - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;MARILYN MANSON - KILL4ME - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie’s Three From Hell - Teaser Trailer - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Twins of Evil - Hell Never Dies Tour 2019 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie AND Marilyn Manson Discuss The First Time They Heard Each Other's Music - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Twins of Evil Tour – The Second Coming - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie - ASTRO-CREEP: 2000 LIVE - OUT NOW! - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie - Vinyl Catalog - Available Now! - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie Career Vinyl Box - OUT NOW! - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie Career Vinyl Box Set - OUT NOW! - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie - ASTRO-CREEP: 2000 LIVE - Available March 30 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie - Vinyl Catalog - Available March 30 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie Career Vinyl Box - Available March 30 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie Career Vinyl Box Set - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie - Get Your Boots On! That's The End Of Rock And Roll! - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie - The Hideous Exhibitions Of A Dedicated Gore Whore - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie - Medication For The Melancholy - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - Desert Queen - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - Chaos Royale - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - Chaos Royale (Lyric) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - 24/7 (Video Commentary) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - Fight Song - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - Hearts of Cold - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - End Of The Line - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - End Of The Line (Lyric video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - 24/7 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - Outrage - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - Rock 'N' Roll (Motörhead Cover) ft. Doro - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - One Out of Ten - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - On Parole - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - Sound of the Underground - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Korn - 'The Nothing' Album Release Concert (Official Extended Film) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Korn - Can You Hear Me (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Korn - Winter 2020 Tour Recap - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Korn - 2019 Docuseries: Episode 06 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Korn - 2019 Docuseries: Episode 05 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Korn - 2019 Docuseries: Episode 04 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Korn - 2019 Docuseries: Episode 03 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Korn - 2019 Docuseries: Episode 02 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Korn - 2019 Docuseries: Episode 01 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Korn - Cold (Official Live Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Korn x Breaking Benjamin 🔲 Winter 2020 North American Tour - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Korn - You'll Never Find Me (Official Live Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Korn - H@rd3r (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Korn - This Loss (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;CKY - Bite It You Scum (Official Music Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;CKY - Wiping Off The Dead - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;CKY - Head For A Breakdown (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;CKY - Replaceable - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;CKY - Days Of Self Destruction - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;CKY - Afterworld (Behind The Scenes) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;CKY - Flesh Into Gear - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;CKY - Familiar Realm - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;CKY - Attached At The Hip (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;CKY - Flesh Into Gear (Blurred Version) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Glitch Mob - Can't Kill Us [2020 Edit] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;29 Palms - Starsplitter - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;29 Palms - Unfolding - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;29 Palms - Nobody Horizon - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;29 Palms - El Circo - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;29 Palms - Metaverse Satellite - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;29 Palms - Microdusk - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Glitch Mob - The Stance - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Glitch Mob - Take Control - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Glitch Mob - Chemicals - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Glitch Mob X 1788-L - Momentary Lapse [Visual] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Glitch Mob X ZEKE BEATS - Lazer Vision [Visual] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Glitch Mob - Alchemy Tour Recap [Part 3] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Steel Panther - Let's Get High Tonight [Official Video] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Steel Panther TV presents: Great Mysteries from History - "The Civil War" - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Steel Panther TV presents: Great Mysteries from History - "The Duel of Hamilton and Burr" - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ladies and Gentlemen, Steel Panther presents The Butthole Burner!! - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Steel Panther TV presents: "The World's Greatest Discoveries: Part Four" - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Steel Panther TV presents: "The World's Greatest Discoveries: Part Three - Gravity" - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Steel Panther 1/2 Hour Power Hour (LIVE from Newcastle, UK) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Power hour - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Steel Panther 1/2 Hour Power Hour (LIVE from Bristol, UK) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Steel Panther 1/2 Hour Power Hour (LIVE from Munich, Germany) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Steel Panther 1/2 Hour Power Hour (Live from Stockholm, SE) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Steel Panther - Heavy Metal Rules [Official Video] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Steel Panther 1/2 Hour Power Hour (LIVE from Madison, WI) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slash ft Myles Kennedy AND The Conspirators - The Call Of The Wild (Living The Dream) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slash ft Myles Kennedy AND The Conspirators - Shadow Life (Living The Dream) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slash Ft. Myles Kennedy AND The Conspirators - Living The Dream Tour (ORDER NOW) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slash ft. Myles Kennedy AND The Conspirators – Living The Dream Tour Teaser (Order Now) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slash ft. Myles Kennedy AND The Conspirators – Anastasia (Living The Dream Tour) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slash ft. Myles Kennedy AND The Conspirators: Behind-the-Scenes at Download Festival 2019 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slash ft. Myles Kennedy AND The Conspirators - "Boulevard of Broken Hearts" Official Music Video - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slash ft. Myles Kennedy AND The Conspirators – Euro Tour 2019: Behind-the-Scenes in Berlin - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slash ft. Myles Kennedy AND The Conspirators – Euro Tour 2019: Behind-the-Scenes in Paris - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slash ft. Myles Kennedy AND The Conspirators – Euro Tour 2019: Behind-the-Scenes in Lodz - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slash ft  Myles Kennedy AND The Conspirators - "Mind Your Manners" Official Music Video - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;SLASH FT. MYLES KENNEDY AND THE CONSPIRATORS - "Driving Rain" Official Music Video - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;SLASH FT. MYLES KENNEDY AND THE CONSPIRATORS - "The Great Pretender" Full Song Static Video - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;SLASH FT. MYLES KENNEDY AND THE CONSPIRATORS - "The One You Loved Is Gone" Full Song Static Video - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;SLASH FT. MYLES KENNEDY AND THE CONSPIRATORS - "Read Between The Lines" Full Song Static Video - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge: Metalingus (Official Lyric Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge: Before Tomorrow Comes - Orchestra Only (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge: Godspeed (Official Lyric Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Myles Kennedy performs "Hallelujah" with Jeff Buckley's Fender Telecaster. - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge: Walk The Sky (In the Studio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge: Dying Light (OFFICIAL VIDEO) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge: Walk The Sky - In The Studio - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge: "Wouldn't You Rather" Track By Track - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge: In The Deep (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge: Take The Crown (Official) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge: Pay No Mind (Official) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge: Open Your Eyes (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge: Wouldn't You Rather (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;"Words Darker Than Their Wings"  Alter Bridge: Orchestra Only (OFFICIAL VIDEO) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge:  "The End Is Here"  Live At The Royal Albert Hall (OFFICIAL VIDEO) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - Always There (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - The March Of The Peaceful Army begins - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - Highway Tune (Live) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - Safari Song (Live) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - Edge Of Darkness (Live) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - You’re The One (Live on SNL / 2019) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - Black Smoke Rising (Live on SNL / 2019) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - You're The One (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - Anthem Of The Peaceful Army Animation Clip - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - The Cold Wind (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - The New Day (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - Mountain of the Sun (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - Age of Man (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - Brave New World (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - Lover, Leaver (Taker, Believer) (Live) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System Of A Down - Bounce (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System of a Down - Toazted Interview 2002 (Daron, part 1) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System of a Down - Toazted Interview 2002 (Daron, part 2) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System of a Down - Toazted Interview 2002 (Daron, part 3) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System of a Down - Toazted Interview 2002 (Daron, part 4) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System of a Down - Toazted Interview 2001 (Shavo, part 3) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System of a Down - Toazted Interview 2001 (Shavo, part 1) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System of a Down - Toazted Interview 2001 (Shavo, part 2) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System of a Down - Toazted Interview 2001 (whole band, part 1) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System of a Down - Toazted Interview 2001 (whole band, part 3) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System of a Down - Toazted Interview 2001 (whole band, part 2) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System Of A Down - Lonely Day (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System Of A Down - Aerials (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System Of A Down - B.Y.O.B. (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System Of A Down - Question! (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;POWERMAN 5000 'Black Lipstick' teaser - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;POWERMAN 5000 West Coast Death Ray Fun Time Invasion Tour - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;POWERMAN 5000 - Footsteps and Voices - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Powerman 5000 - David Fucking Bowie - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;POWERMAN 5000 - "Cult Leader" - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Powerman 5000 - Sid Vicious in a Dress - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;POWERMAN 5000 - "Sid Vicious In A Dress" (audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;POWERMAN 5000 - "Invade Destroy Repeat" (official video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Powerman 5000 - How To Be A Human - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Powerman 5000 - How To Be A Human (Lyric Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Powerman 5000 - Bombshell - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Powerman 5000 - Tokyo Vigilante #1 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Powerman 5000 - Nobody's Real (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Powerman 5000 - Super Villain - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Powerman 5000 - Free - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea, Pabllo Vittar - The Girls (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea - Personal Problem (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea - Not Important (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;"Lola" Music Video Behind The Scenes - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea, Alice Chater - Lola (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea - Behind The Scenes: Iggy Azalea "In My Defense" Album Release Week - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea - Thanks I Get (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea - Comme Des Garcons (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea - Pussy Pop (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea - Spend It (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea - Hoemita (Audio) ft. Lil Yachty - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea - Freak Of The Week (Audio) ft. Juicy J - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea - Big Bag (Audio) ft. Stini - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea - Clap Back (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea - F*ck It Up (Official Music Video) ft. Kash Doll - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande AND Justin Bieber - Stuck with U (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande - Live at The 62nd GRAMMYs ® (2020) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande - dangerous woman (swt live) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande - needy (swt live) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande - fake smile (swt live) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande - bad idea (swt live) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande - 7 rings (swt live) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande - into you (swt live) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande - successful (swt live) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande - only 1 (swt live) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande - side to side (swt live) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande -  thank u, next (swt live) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande - make up (swt live) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande - nasa (swt live) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande - everytime (swt live) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;MAD SIN - Are You Ready? (Visualizer) - Contained not followed artist.
&lt;br&gt;CARYS  - No More [Official Lyric Video] - Contained not followed artist.
&lt;br&gt;Behind the Scenes with Godsmack’s Unforgettable - Contained GENERIC phrase: Behind the scenes.
&lt;br&gt;Godsmack - Unforgettable - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Godsmack Unforgettable 2020 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sully Erna AND The Scars Foundation Brings an Early Christmas for 3 Lucky Kids - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;"Under Your Scars" - Godsmack - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Scars Foundation Call to Action from Sully Erna - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Godsmack 2019 European Tour - Backstage Warm Ups - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Godsmack 2019 European Tour - Robbie's Worst Hits - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;"When Legends Rise" - Godsmack - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Godsmack - Unforgettable (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Godsmack - Take It To The Edge (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Godsmack - Every Part Of Me (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Godsmack - Under Your Scars (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;IHeartRadio LIVE with Godsmack ! - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;GODSMACK - When Legends Rise (Studio Update #1) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Katy Perry - Daisies (Lyric Video) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Lyric Video.
&lt;br&gt;Katy Perry - Never Really Over (Live on Good Morning America / 2020) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Live.
&lt;br&gt;Katy Perry - Daisies (Live On Good Morning America) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Live.
&lt;br&gt;Katy Perry - Daisies (Live From American Idol Finale, May 17 2020) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Live.
&lt;br&gt;Katy Perry - Never Worn White (Official) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Katy Perry - Making Of "Cozy Little Christmas" Music Video - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Katy Perry - Cozy Little Christmas - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Katy Perry - Surprises A Biker In A Dramatic Reading Of Harleys In Hawaii - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Katy Perry - Harleys In Hawaii (Vertical Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Katy Perry - Making Of "Harleys In Hawaii" Music Video - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Katy Perry - ASMR: Harleys In Hawaii - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;THE HU: Road to The Gereg - Contained not followed artist.
&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish - ilomilo (Visualizer) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish - when the party’s over (Live at Coachella 2019) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish - No Time To Die (Live From The BRIT Awards, London) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish - No Time To Die (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish - you should see me in a crown (Live From Austin City Limits) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish - bad guy (Live From Austin City Limits) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish - when the party's over (Live From The Grammys) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish - everything i wanted - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish - come out and play (LIVE FROM THE STEVE JOBS THEATER) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish - listen before i go (LIVE FROM THE STEVE JOBS THEATER) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish - everything i wanted (LIVE FROM MEXICO CITY) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish - xanny - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish - all the good girls go to hell (Live From The American Music Awards/2019) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish - everything i wanted (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;MAD SIN - Are You Ready? (Visualizer) - Contained not followed artist.
&lt;br&gt;Madonna - Hung Up (Live at Coachella 2006) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Live.
&lt;br&gt;Madonna - Vogue (Live from the Sticky AND Sweet Tour) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Madonna - Vogue ('I'm Going To Tell You A Secret' documentary version) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Madonna - Vogue (Live from The Blond Ambition Tour) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Madonna - Vogue (Strike A Pose Dub) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Madonna - Vogue (Bette Davis Dub) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Madonna - Vogue (12" Version) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Madonna AND Maluma - Medellín (2019 Billboard Music Awards) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Madonna - Like A Virgin (Extended Dance Remix) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Madonna - Material Girl (Extended Dance Remix) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Madonna - Angel (Extended Dance Mix) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Madonna - Dress You Up (12'' Formal Mix) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Madonna - Crave (Twisted Dee AND Diego Fernandez Remix/Audio) ft. Swae Lee - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Madonna - Crave (Otto Benson Remix/Audio) ft. Swae Lee - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Die Antwoord - Future Baby (Official Music Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Die Antwoord #VeganAF - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Die Antwoord - LAMBO LIFE (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Die Antwoord - BANG ON EM (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Die Antwoord - HO$H HO$H HO$H feat Bobajan, Skelm (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Die Antwoord - WHEN THE SUN GOES OUT feat. Roger Ballen (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Die Antwoord - ZONKE BONKE feat. Bukhulubakhe, Gqwa! (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Die Antwoord - MY LIFE IS A PORNO feat. Smiley (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Die Antwoord - DA GODZ MUS B KRAZY (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Die Antwoord - FUTURE BABY (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;DIE ANTWOORD - HOUSE OF ZEF - MEGAMIX9000 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Die Antwoord - DON'T SLEEP (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Die Antwoord - OPEN THE DOOR feat. Panther Modern (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Die Antwoord - NAAI IS 'N LEKKER DING feat. Moonchild Sanelly, Gqwa!, JouMaSePoes (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Die Antwoord - NO 1 (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;A Light or a Distant Mirror Official Preshow w/ Beez - Contained not followed artist.
&lt;br&gt;EUROPE STADIUM TOUR RESCHEDULED TO 2021! - Contained GENERIC phrase: Tour.
&lt;br&gt;Rammstein - Making Of Album-Photosession (Official) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Making of.
&lt;br&gt;Rammstein - Europe Stadium Tour (Time Lapse) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rammstein Zeppelin - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rammstein - North America Stadium Tour 2020 (On Sale Now) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Get ready, Amerika! - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rammstein - Ausländer (Official Making Of) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rammstein App (Official) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rammstein - Radio (Official Making Of) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rammstein - Ausländer (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rammstein - Stripped (Official Making Of) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rammstein - Stripped (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rammstein - Radio (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;HALLOMANN - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;TATTOO - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - Back In Black / Highway To Hell (Live) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - Whole Lotta Rosie (from Countdown, 1979) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - Night Prowler (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - Love Hungry Man (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - Roadmap of Highway to Hell (from the film The Story of Back In Black) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - Beating Around the Bush (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - Get It Hot (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - The Jack (from Countdown, 1979) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - Highway to Hell 40th Anniversary Trailer - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - Highway to Hell (from Countdown, 1979) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - Highway to Hell (Live at Donington, 8/17/91) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - Dirty Deeds Done Dirt Cheap (Live at Donington, 8/17/91) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - Whole Lotta Rosie (Plaza De Toros De Las Ventas, July 1996) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - You Shook Me All Night Long (Plaza De Toros De Las Ventas, Ju... - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - Let There Be Rock (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Static-X Official 20th Anniversary Wisconsin Death Trip World Tour PROMO - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Wisconsin Death Trip 20th Anniversary Tour - Australia - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Wisconsin Death Trip 20 Year Anniversary Tour / Static-X / Devil Driver / Dope / Wayne Memorial - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Eminem - Godzilla (Lyric Video) ft. Juice WRLD - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Premonition - Intro [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Unaccommodating (feat. Young M.A) [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;You Gon' Learn (feat. Royce Da 5'9" AND White Gold) [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;In Too Deep [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Those Kinda Nights (feat. Ed Sheeran) [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Godzilla (feat. Juice WRLD) [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Darkness [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Leaving Heaven (feat. Skylar Grey) [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Yah Yah (feat. Royce Da 5'9", Black Thought, Q-Tip AND Denaun) [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Stepdad [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Marsh [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Never Love Again [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Lock It Up (feat. Anderson .Paak) [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Little Engine [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - I'm Good? (Official Lyrics Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - The Great Expanse World Tour (North America Tour Diary) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - ‘The Great Expanse’ World Tour Europe AND UK Part 6 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - ‘The Great Expanse’ World Tour Europe AND UK Part 5 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - ‘The Great Expanse’ World Tour Europe AND UK Part 4 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - The Great Expanse’ World Tour Europe AND UK Part 3 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - ‘The Great Expanse’ World Tour Europe AND UK Part 2 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - ‘The Great Expanse’ World Tour Europe AND UK Pt. 1 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - Biggest Headline Show! Sydney Australia, Qudas Bank Arena - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - Brisbane Australia, Riverstage Night 2 (The Great Expanse World Tour) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - Brisbane Australia, Riverstage Night 1 (The Great Expanse World Tour) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - Adelaide Australia, AEC (The Great Expanse World Tour) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - Melbourne Australia, Rod Laver Arena Round 2 (The Great Expanse World Tour) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - Melbourne Australia, Rod Laver Arena Night 1 (The Great Expanse World Tour) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - Queenstown New Zealand, July 2019 (The Great Expanse World Tour) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Foo Fighters - Live at Wembley Stadium (2008)(Full Concert) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Live.
&lt;br&gt;Foo Fighters - Skin And Bones (2006) (Full Concert) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Foo Fighters - Live in Hyde Park (2006) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Cal Jam 18 - More Good Times! - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;FOO FIGHTERS | 25 YEARS - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Foo Fighters - Everlong (from Skin And Bones, Live in Hollywood, 2006) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Foo Fighters - What If I Do? (from Skin And Bones, Live in Hollywood, 2006) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Foo Fighters - Best Of You (from Skin And Bones, Live in Hollywood, 2006) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Foo Fighters - February Stars (from Skin And Bones, Live in Hollywood, 2006) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Foo Fighters - Times Like These (from Skin And Bones, Live in Hollywood, 2006) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Foo Fighters - Big Me (from Skin And Bones, Live in Hollywood, 2006) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Foo Fighters - Friend Of A Friend (from Skin And Bones, Live in Hollywood, 2006) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Foo Fighters - See You (from Skin And Bones, Live in Hollywood, 2006) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Foo Fighters - Ain't It The Life (from Skin And Bones, Live in Hollywood, 2006) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Foo Fighters - Cold Day In The Sun (from Skin And Bones, Live in Hollywood, 2006) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys - 'Let's Rock' [Record Store Day 2020] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys - 'Let's Rock' MasterCourse - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys - "Let's Rock" Voicemail #8 [1-740-303-ROCK] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys - Detroit 'Let's Rock' Tour Poster - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys - "Let's Rock" Voicemail #4 [1-740-303-ROCK] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys - "Let's Rock" Voicemail #3 [1-740-303-ROCK] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys – Eagle Birds ["Let's Rock" Tour Rehearsals] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys - "Let's Rock" [Promo #21] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys - I Got Mine ["Let's Rock" Tour Rehearsals] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys - Lonely Boy ["Let's Rock" Tour Rehearsals] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys - “Let’s Rock” Tour Promo [St. Louis #1] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys - “Let’s Rock” Tour Promo [Denver #2] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys - "Let's Rock" Voicemail #2 [1-740-303-ROCK] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys - "Let's Rock" [Promo #20] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys - "Let's Rock" [Promo #19] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Albo inaczej - Paulina Przybysz - Trzeba było zostać dresiarą - Contained not followed artist.

&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
<dc:creator> &lt;a&gt;Bednar&lt;/a&gt;</dc:creator>
</item>
</rdf:RDF>