<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<rdf:RDF
 xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#"
 xmlns="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/"
 xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
 xmlns:taxo="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/taxonomy/"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:syn="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
 xmlns:admin="http://webns.net/mvcb/"
>
<channel rdf:about="http://spotify.com/">
<title>Spotify new releases</title>
<link>http://spotify.com/</link>
<description rdf:parseType="Literal">Releases of followed artists on Spotify</description>
<dc:language>en-us</dc:language>
<dc:date>2018-03-07T20:30:00-05:00</dc:date>
<dc:publisher>help@spotify.com</dc:publisher>
<dc:subject>Music</dc:subject>
<syn:updateBase>1901-01-01T00:00+00:00</syn:updateBase>
<syn:updateFrequency>1</syn:updateFrequency>
<syn:updatePeriod>daily</syn:updatePeriod>
<items>
 <rdf:Seq>
<rdf:li rdf:resource="http://spotify.com"/></rdf:Seq>
</items>
<image rdf:resource="https://www.scdn.co/i/_global/favicon.png" />
</channel>
<image rdf:about="https://www.scdn.co/i/_global/favicon.png">
<title>Spotify releases</title>
<url>https://www.scdn.co/i/_global/favicon.png</url>
<link>http://spotify.com</link>
</image><item rdf:about="http://spotify.com">
<title>2021-03-01 11:54 YouTube newest rejects</title>
<link>http://spotify.com</link>
<description rdf:parseType="Literal">&lt;p&gt;New releases:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Slipknot Whiskey | Bottle Signing w/ Clown, Vman AND NG - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot Whiskey Bottle Signing - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - Unsainted (Behind The Scenes) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - Pollution - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - Nero Forte [OFFICIAL VIDEO] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - Europe AND UK 2020 Tour Announce - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Alexa: Play 'We Are Not Your Kind' by Slipknot (Amazon Music) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - Insert Coin (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - Death Because of Death (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - Red Flag (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - Not Long For This World (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - Critical Darling (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - Spiders (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - My Pain (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - Orphan (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - Love Story (Taylor’s Version) [Official Lyric Video] - Contained GENERIC phrase: Lyric Video.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - right where you left me (Official Lyric Video) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Lyric Video.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - it’s time to go (Official Lyric Video) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Lyric Video.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - willow (moonlit witch version) - [yule log] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - willow (lonely witch version) - [yule log] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - willow (dancing witch version) - [yule log] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - willow - [yule log] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - willow (moonlit witch version) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - willow (dancing witch version) - storyboards from the willow music video - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - willow (lonely witch version) - music video behind the scenes - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - willow - dancing witch version (Elvira remix) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - dorothea (Official Lyric Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - champagne problems (Official Lyric Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - tolerate it (Official Lyric Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - cowboy like me (Official Lyric Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;SUMMONING THE LICH - THE GATEKEEPER (OFFICIAL AUDIO) - Contained not followed artist.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic - Magic (Official Lyric Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;MAGIC out today! - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic - Superlove (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;RoyalRepublic - We Are The Royal Special - Live Stream from KB | #StayHome and DANCE #WithMe - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic - Anna-Leigh (Club Majesty Live@Rockpalast) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic - Fireman AND Dancer (Club Majesty Live@Rockpalast) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic - Getting Along (Club Majesty Live@Rockpalast) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic - Baby (Club Majesty Live@Rockpalast) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic feat. Ralf Gyllenhammar - Double Nature (Club Majesty Live@Stockholm) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic - Club Majesty Tour 2019/2020 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic - Stop Movin' (Club Majesy Live@Skärgårdsfest) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic - What a summer! Can't wait to kick off the Club Majesty European Tour in October! - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic - Like A Lover (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic - Anna-Leigh (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic - Boomerang (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;GOJIRA - Hellfest 2019 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Live from Hellfest 2019  FREE STREAM 18th November - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Gojira - Inferno Live (From Maciste All Inferno 2003) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Gojira - All The Tears [OFFICIAL VIDEO 2009] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Gojira - Vacuity [OFFICIAL VIDEO 2008] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Gojira - To Sirius [OFFICIAL VIDEO 2005] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Gojira - Another World [OFFICIAL VIDEO] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Gojira #Anewplaceforme - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Gojira #anotherplacetobe - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Gojira at Red Rocks - PRAY (extended version) LIVE - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mario Duplantier - Drum solo Bloodstock 2018 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;GOJIRA - Pol'And'Rock Festival 2018 [LIVE] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;GOJIRA - Bloodstock 2018 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;GOJIRA - Into The Grave Festival 2018 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Post Malone AND Red Hot Chili Peppers - Stay / Rockstar / Dark Necessities [LIVE at the 61st GRAMMYs] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Flea On RHCP Fans [The Getaway Track-By-Track Commentary] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Flea On His Preshow Rituals  [The Getaway Track-By-Track Commentary] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Goodbye Angels [Official Music Video] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Chad On His Preshow Rituals [The Getaway Track-By-Track Commentary] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Flea on Free Time Between Albums [The Getaway Track-By-Track Commentary] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Anthony on Relationship with Fans [The Getaway Track-By-Track Commentary] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Josh's Preshow Rituals [The Getaway Track-By-Track Commentary] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Anthony On Working With Brian Burton [The Getaway Track-By-Track Commentary] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Anthony's Preshow Rituals [The Getaway Track-By-Track Commentary] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Sick Love [Official Music Video] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Anthony Explains the Album Title [The Getaway Track-By-Track Commentary] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Flea on the Energy of the Live Shows [The Getaway Track-By-Track Commentary] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - The Getaway [Live Download from Munich, Germany 11.01.16] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Nobody Weird Like Me [Live Download from Munich, Germany 11.01.16] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak: Julablot (Kids React) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;SPLID: The Album - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak- Rogaland Live at Lindmo - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak: Recording SPLID (Part 2) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak: Recording SPLID (Part 1) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak - Bronsegud [OFFICIAL VIDEO] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak - Svartmesse [OFFICIAL VIDEO] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak - Nattesferd [OFFICIAL VIDEO] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak - Heksebrann (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak - Berserkr (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak - Dendrofil for Yggdrasil (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak - Ondskapens Galakse (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak - Nekrodamus (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak - Svartmesse (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak - Nattesferd (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Silk City - New Love (feat. Ellie Goulding) [Live on The Graham Norton Show] - Contained GENERIC phrase: Live.
&lt;br&gt;Silk City - New Love (feat. Ellie Goulding) [Behind The Scenes] - Contained GENERIC phrase: Behind the scenes.
&lt;br&gt;Silk City - New Love (feat. Ellie Goulding) (Official Lyric Video) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Lyric Video.
&lt;br&gt;Ellie Goulding - River (Acoustic) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ellie Goulding - Anything Could Happen (Fan Lyric Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ellie Goulding - Love I’m Given (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ellie Goulding, Lauv - Slow Grenade | Official Live Performance | Vevo - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ellie Goulding - Start feat. serpentwithfeet (Live) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Behind Brightest Blue with Ellie Goulding - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ellie Goulding - New Heights | Official Live Performance | Vevo - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ellie Goulding - Close To Me (Live On "Good Morning America", New York / 2020) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ellie Goulding - Woman (Live On "Good Morning America", New York / 2020) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ellie Goulding - Slow Grenade (Live On "Good Morning America", New York / 2020) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit - Toazted Interview 1998 (part 2) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit - Toazted Interview 1998 (part 1) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit - Toazted Interview 1998 (part 3) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit - Toazted Interview 1998 (part 4) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Endless Slaughter (Official Visual 2014) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;LIGHTZ (Official Video) - Limp Bizkit - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit "Behind Blue Eyes" - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit "Boiler" - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit "Break Stuff" - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit "Eat You Alive" - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit "My Way" - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit "Faith" REMIX - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit - Ready To Go (Official Music Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit - Lightz - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit - Ready To Go ft. Lil Wayne (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ahmed ag Kaedy and Embryo - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Embryo live February 2017 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Embryo feat. Deobrat and Prashant Mishra 2017 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Embryo - Mal Waldron -  Memorial Concert - Left Alone - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Embryo in the Seventies, Vlotho 78 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Embryo in the Seventies, Feature, WDR 1980 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Embryo and Friends, La Pirata, Llanca, Spain, 21.02.2016 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Embryo + Wieland Rehm - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Embryo live, Embryokeller München 09.Januar 2016 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Embryo and Mal Waldron, TU Mensa Munich,  29. Nov. 1990 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;ADM - Free-Haven - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mal Waldron AND Embryo, 20 Jahrfeier, Part I - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mal Waldron AND Embryo, 20 Jahrfeier, Part II - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Embryo - Agnessession - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Roman Bunka AND Christian Burchard - Sunsong - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Cooking With Mastodon - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Cooking With Mastodon - Dirty B Hinds - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Cooking With Mastodon - Billy "The Culinarian (Barbarian)" Kelliher - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Cooking With Mastodon - Brann Dailor - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Cooking With Mastodon - Chef Troyardee - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - Fallen Torches [Official Music Video] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - Iron Tusk (Live) [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - Cut You Up [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - Halloween (Instrumental) [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - Asleep in the Deep (Instrumental) [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - A Spoonful Weighs A Ton [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - A Commotion [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - Jaguar God [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - Toe to Toes (Instrumental) [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga, Bruno Martini - 911 (Bruno Martini Remix/Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga, Sofi Tukker - 911 (Sofi Tukker Remix/Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga, WEISS - 911 (WEISS Remix/Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga - The Making of '911' | Vevo Footnotes - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;howto.vote - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;NEW BLUSH + BRONZER DUOS FOR HAUS LABS | A STUDY OF ATTRACTION - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga - 911 (Short Film) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga - VMA Performance 2020 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga, Honey Dijon - Free Woman (Honey Dijon Realness Remix/Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga, Ariana Grande, Ralphi Rosario - Rain On Me (Ralphi Rosario Remix/Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rain On Me (Purple Disco Machine Remix/Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga, BLACKPINK - Sour Candy (Lyric Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga - Chromatica III (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga - Babylon (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga - Fun Tonight (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;P!NK - A Million Dreams (with Ndlovu Youth Choir) [UNICEF Changemaker 2020] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - Hurts 2B Human (Kat Krazy Remix (Audio)) ft. Khalid - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - Hurts 2B Human (FTampa Remix (Audio)) ft. Khalid - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - Hurts 2B Human (Alex Ghenea Remix (Audio)) ft. Khalid - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - Hurts 2B Human (Midnight Kids Remix (Audio)) ft. Khalid - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - Hurts 2B Human (Frank Pole Remix (Audio)) ft. Khalid - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - Hurts 2B Human feat. Khalid - Behind The Scenes - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - Hurts 2B Human ft. Khalid - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - Can We Pretend (Animated Video) ft. Cash Cash - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - Can We Pretend (Sigala Remix (Audio)) ft. Cash Cash - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - 90 Days (Official Video) ft. Wrabel - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - Walk Me Home (Dinaire+Bissen Remix (Audio)) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - Walk Me Home (R3HAB Extended Mix (Audio)) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - Walk Me Home (Until Dawn Remix (Audio)) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;NOCNY KOCHANEK - ALKUSTYCZNIE (2020) (CAŁY ALBUM) (OFICJALNY ODSŁUCH) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;01. Nocny Kochanek - Poniedzieli (Oficjalny Odsłuch Albumu) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;02. Nocny Kochanek - Poniedziałek (Oficjalny Odsłuch Albumu) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;03. Nocny Kochanek - Łatwa Nie Była (Oficjalny Odsłuch Albumu) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;04. Nocny Kochanek - Andżeju (Oficjalny Odsłuch Albumu) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;05. Nocny Kochanek - Mistrz Przerósł Ucznia (Oficjalny Odsłuch Albumu) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;06. Nocny Kochanek - Pierwszego Nie Przepijam (Oficjalny Odsłuch Albumu) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;07. Nocny Kochanek - Koń Na Białym Rycerzu (Oficjalny Odsłuch Albumu) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;08. Nocny Kochanek - Wielki Wojownik (Oficjalny Odsłuch Albumu) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;09. Nocny Kochanek - Zdrajca Metalu (Oficjalny Odsłuch Albumu) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;10. Nocny Kochanek - Minerał Fiutta (Oficjalny Odsłuch Albumu) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;11. Nocny Kochanek - Gdzie Jesteś (Oficjalny Odsłuch Albumu) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Nocny Kochanek i Michał Wiśniewski - Zdrajca Metalu - Warszawa @Torwar - Odcinek 4 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Przegryw z Kazonem (Nocny Kochanek) - Siłacze S01E011 (PLAYTHROUGH) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Home for the Weekend - Berkeley w Neal Brennan AND The Lonely Island (Pilot Presentation) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Let's Bash | The Unauthorized Bash Brothers Experience - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Alexa, play me some hot garbage (this actually works) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Uniform On | The Unauthorized Bash Brothers Experience - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Oakland Nights (feat. Sia) | The Unauthorized Bash Brothers Experience - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Lil' Tour Announcement - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;OSCAR SONG DEMO - "Why Not Me?" - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Jack Sparrow Unplugged (from Michael Bolton's Netflix Special) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Old Time Rock N Roll (from Netflix's Michael Bolton's Big Sexy Valentine's Day Special) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Natalie's Rap 2.0 (Uncensored Version) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;I'm On A Boat - Classroom Instruments w Jimmy Fallon AND The Roots - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Shy Ronnie (ft. Rihanna) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;conner4real Radio Freestyle - Big Boy (92.3) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Lazy Sunday Live w/ The Roots - Late Night w Jimmy Fallon - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;conner4real - "F**k Off" (Popstar Deleted Scene/Song) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Christina Aguilera, A Great Big World - Fall On Me - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;A Great Big World AND Christina Aguilera - Fall On Me (Live from the 2019 AMAs) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Christina Aguilera - Haunted Heart (Lyric Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Christina Aguilera: The Xperience - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Christina Aguilera - Like I Do (Lyric Video) ft. GoldLink - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Christina Aguilera - Fall In Line feat. Demi Lovato - Behind The Scenes - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Christina Aguilera - Like I Do (Audio) ft. GoldLink - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Christina Aguilera - Fall In Line (Official Video) ft. Demi Lovato - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Christina Aguilera - Fall In Line (Lyric Video) ft. Demi Lovato - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Christina Aguilera - Twice (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Where’s Maria? (Liberation by Christina Aguilera) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Christina Aguilera - Accelerate (Official Video) ft. Ty Dolla $ign, 2 Chainz - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Christina Aguilera - Ven Conmigo (Solamente Tú) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Christina Aguilera - Telepathy (feat. Nile Rodgers) [Fan Video] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine (Making Of Loteria 🎯) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine  - Loteria 🎯 (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine #Hot16Challenge2 💉 (MC Pauletta/MC Krychu/MC Skiplex) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine - Kamuflaże 🍷 (Quarantine Edition) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine - Znak 🔑 (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Przebój Rocku Antyradia - "Jak Ci Powiedzieć?"🎸 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine - Błyski ⚡ (Lyric Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine - Jak Ci Powiedzieć? 🎱 (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine - Odchodząc 🏁 (Republika Cover) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine - Pretending 🔮 (Official Live Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine - Neverland 🍂 (Official Live Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine - Secret Self 🎭 (Live ❣ WOŚP ❣ Sanok) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine - Dicegame 🎲(Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine - Broken 🖤 (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;RAU_PERFORMANCE - SOUND OF VICTORY - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;RAU_PERFORMANCE #HOT16CHALLENGE2 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;RAU_PERFORMANCE - NIECH MNIE KTOS USZCZYPNIE - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;TECHNOTORIOUS R.A.U. - ROLEX WATCHES - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;PŁOMIEŃ 81 - POWIEDZ NA OSIEDLU – INTERPRETACJE / zapowiedź - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Proseko - Wsiadam do auta (prod. megot) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;RAU_PERFORMANCE - ODKRYJ W SOBIE LATO. - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;RAU_PERFORMANCE - FYI (INTRO) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;RAU_PERFORMANCE - NIKT W POLSCE. - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;RAU_PERFORMANCE - ŚCIANA - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;RAU_PERFORMANCE - DOJADAMY (FT. KSIĄŻE KAPOTA, FROSTI REGE, ŻYTO) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;RAU_PERFORMANCE - MISTRZ_SZTUKI. - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;EN2AK FT. RAU - GUMOWA KACZKA [POLAKPOTRAFI.PL] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;RAU_PERFORMANCE - NIE DZWOŃ, NIE PISZ. - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;🍄 ŚMIESZNY GRZYB 🍄 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Marilyn Manson - DON'T CHASE THE DEAD (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Marilyn Manson - Apple Music 'WE ARE CHAOS' Interview - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Marilyn Manson - SOLVE COAGULA (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Marilyn Manson - INFINITE DARKNESS (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Marilyn Manson - PAINT YOU WITH MY LOVE (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Marilyn Manson - PERFUME (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Marilyn Manson - RED, BLACK AND BLUE (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;MARILYN MANSON - KEEP MY HEAD TOGETHER (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Marilyn Manson - BROKEN NEEDLE (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Marilyn Manson - HALF-WAY AND ONE STEP FORWARD (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Marilyn Manson - DON'T CHASE THE DEAD (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Marilyn Manson - WE ARE CHAOS (Official Music Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;PREPARE - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Marilyn Manson - Personal Jesus (Live) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Marilyn Manson - God's Gonna Cut You Down (Official Music Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie’s Three From Hell - Teaser Trailer - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Twins of Evil - Hell Never Dies Tour 2019 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie AND Marilyn Manson Discuss The First Time They Heard Each Other's Music - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Twins of Evil Tour – The Second Coming - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie - ASTRO-CREEP: 2000 LIVE - OUT NOW! - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie - Vinyl Catalog - Available Now! - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie Career Vinyl Box - OUT NOW! - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie Career Vinyl Box Set - OUT NOW! - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie - ASTRO-CREEP: 2000 LIVE - Available March 30 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie - Vinyl Catalog - Available March 30 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie Career Vinyl Box - Available March 30 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie Career Vinyl Box Set - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie - Get Your Boots On! That's The End Of Rock And Roll! - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie - The Hideous Exhibitions Of A Dedicated Gore Whore - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie - Medication For The Melancholy - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - Desert Queen - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - Chaos Royale - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - Chaos Royale (Lyric) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - 24/7 (Video Commentary) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - Fight Song - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - Hearts of Cold - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - End Of The Line - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - End Of The Line (Lyric video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - 24/7 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - Outrage - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - Rock 'N' Roll (Motörhead Cover) ft. Doro - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - One Out of Ten - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - On Parole - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - Sound of the Underground - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Korn - Making of "Black Is The Soul" - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Korn - Finally Free (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Korn - Can You Hear Me (Acoustic) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Korn - 'The Nothing' Album Release Concert (Official Extended Film) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Korn - Can You Hear Me (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Korn - Winter 2020 Tour Recap - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Korn - 2019 Docuseries: Episode 06 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Korn - 2019 Docuseries: Episode 05 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Korn - 2019 Docuseries: Episode 04 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Korn - 2019 Docuseries: Episode 03 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Korn - 2019 Docuseries: Episode 02 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Korn - 2019 Docuseries: Episode 01 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Korn - Cold (Official Live Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Korn x Breaking Benjamin 🔲 Winter 2020 North American Tour - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Korn - You'll Never Find Me (Official Live Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;CKY - Bite It You Scum (Official Music Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;CKY - Wiping Off The Dead - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;CKY - Head For A Breakdown (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;CKY - Replaceable - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;CKY - Days Of Self Destruction - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;CKY - Afterworld (Behind The Scenes) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;CKY - Flesh Into Gear - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;CKY - Familiar Realm - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;CKY - Attached At The Hip (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;CKY - Flesh Into Gear (Blurred Version) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Steel Panther - Fuck 2020 [Official Video] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Steel Panther HalloweenieRide LiveScream: Screaming on VOD through November 14th! - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Steel Panther - Let's Get High Tonight (Black Metal) [Official Video] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Steel Panther: 'Rockdown In The Lockdown' Available On Demand Through August 31st! - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Steel Panther TV presents: Great Mysteries from History - "The Invention of the Telephone" - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Steel Panther: "Rockdown In The Lockdown" Virtual Concert Happening August 16th!! - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Steel Panther - Let's Get High Tonight (Boy Band Version) [Official Video] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Steel Panther TV presents: Great Mysteries from History - "The Sinking of the Titanic" - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Steel Panther - Let's Get High Tonight [Official Video] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Steel Panther TV presents: Great Mysteries from History - "The Civil War" - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Steel Panther TV presents: Great Mysteries from History - "The Duel of Hamilton and Burr" - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ladies and Gentlemen, Steel Panther presents The Butthole Burner!! - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Steel Panther TV presents: "The World's Greatest Discoveries: Part Four" - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Steel Panther TV presents: "The World's Greatest Discoveries: Part Three - Gravity" - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Steel Panther 1/2 Hour Power Hour (LIVE from Newcastle, UK) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slash ft Myles Kennedy AND The Conspirators - The Call Of The Wild (Living The Dream) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slash ft Myles Kennedy AND The Conspirators - Shadow Life (Living The Dream) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slash Ft. Myles Kennedy AND The Conspirators - Living The Dream Tour (ORDER NOW) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slash ft. Myles Kennedy AND The Conspirators – Living The Dream Tour Teaser (Order Now) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slash ft. Myles Kennedy AND The Conspirators – Anastasia (Living The Dream Tour) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slash ft. Myles Kennedy AND The Conspirators: Behind-the-Scenes at Download Festival 2019 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slash ft. Myles Kennedy AND The Conspirators - "Boulevard of Broken Hearts" Official Music Video - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slash ft. Myles Kennedy AND The Conspirators – Euro Tour 2019: Behind-the-Scenes in Berlin - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slash ft. Myles Kennedy AND The Conspirators – Euro Tour 2019: Behind-the-Scenes in Paris - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slash ft. Myles Kennedy AND The Conspirators – Euro Tour 2019: Behind-the-Scenes in Lodz - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slash ft  Myles Kennedy AND The Conspirators - "Mind Your Manners" Official Music Video - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;SLASH FT. MYLES KENNEDY AND THE CONSPIRATORS - "Driving Rain" Official Music Video - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;SLASH FT. MYLES KENNEDY AND THE CONSPIRATORS - "The Great Pretender" Full Song Static Video - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;SLASH FT. MYLES KENNEDY AND THE CONSPIRATORS - "The One You Loved Is Gone" Full Song Static Video - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;SLASH FT. MYLES KENNEDY AND THE CONSPIRATORS - "Read Between The Lines" Full Song Static Video - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mark Tremonti Rig Run Through - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Myles Kennedy Rig Run Through - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Scott Phillips Rig Run Though - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Brian Marshall - Rig Run Through - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;For The Love Of The Music: Brian Marshall - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge: "Last Rites" OFFICIAL VIDEO - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge: Native Son (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge: Metalingus (Official Lyric Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge: Before Tomorrow Comes - Orchestra Only (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge: Godspeed (Official Lyric Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Myles Kennedy performs "Hallelujah" with Jeff Buckley's Fender Telecaster. - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge: Walk The Sky (In the Studio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge: Dying Light (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge: Walk The Sky - In The Studio - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge: "Wouldn't You Rather" Track By Track - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - Heat Above (Audio) - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - Age of Machine (Live) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Live.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - Age of Machine (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - Age of Machine (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - My Way, Soon (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - Live at the Red Rocks Amphitheater: Encore - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - Live at the Red Rocks Amphitheater: Act 3 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - Live at the Red Rocks Amphitheater: Act 2 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - Live at the Red Rocks Amphitheater: Act 1 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - Always There (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - The March Of The Peaceful Army begins - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - Highway Tune (Live in Toronto / 2018) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - Safari Song (Live in Toronto / 2018) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - Edge Of Darkness (Live in Toronto / 2018) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System Of A Down Live Fundraiser For Wounded Armenian Soldiers+ “Genocidal Humanoidz” Video Premiere - Contained GENERIC phrase: Live.
&lt;br&gt;System Of A Down - Protect The Land (Behind The Scenes) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System Of A Down - Speaking Out For Artsakh (Band Interview) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System Of A Down - Genocidal Humanoidz (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System Of A Down - Protect The Land (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System Of A Down - Bounce (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System of a Down - Toazted Interview 2002 (Daron, part 1) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System of a Down - Toazted Interview 2002 (Daron, part 2) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System of a Down - Toazted Interview 2002 (Daron, part 3) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System of a Down - Toazted Interview 2002 (Daron, part 4) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System of a Down - Toazted Interview 2001 (Shavo, part 3) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System of a Down - Toazted Interview 2001 (Shavo, part 1) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System of a Down - Toazted Interview 2001 (Shavo, part 2) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System of a Down - Toazted Interview 2001 (whole band, part 1) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;POWERMAN 5000 'Brave New World' teaser - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;POWERMAN 5000 'Black Lipstick' teaser - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;POWERMAN 5000 West Coast Death Ray Fun Time Invasion Tour - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;POWERMAN 5000 - Footsteps and Voices - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Powerman 5000 - David Fucking Bowie - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;POWERMAN 5000 - "Cult Leader" - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Powerman 5000 - Sid Vicious in a Dress - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;POWERMAN 5000 - "Sid Vicious In A Dress" (audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;POWERMAN 5000 - "Invade Destroy Repeat" (official video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Powerman 5000 - How To Be A Human - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Powerman 5000 - How To Be A Human (Lyric Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Powerman 5000 - Bombshell - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Powerman 5000 - Tokyo Vigilante #1 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Powerman 5000 - Nobody's Real (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Powerman 5000 - Super Villain - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy tastes weird candy canes // BoredGRL TV - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea, Tinashe - Dance Like Nobody's Watching (Official Lyric Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea, Pabllo Vittar - The Girls (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea - Personal Problem (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea - Not Important (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;"Lola" Music Video Behind The Scenes - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea, Alice Chater - Lola (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea - Behind The Scenes: Iggy Azalea "In My Defense" Album Release Week - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea - Thanks I Get (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea - Comme Des Garcons (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea - Pussy Pop (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea - Spend It (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea - Hoemita (Audio) ft. Lil Yachty - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea - Freak Of The Week (Audio) ft. Juicy J - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea - Big Bag (Audio) ft. Stini - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande - main thing (official audio) - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande - worst behavior (official audio) - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande - test drive (official audio) - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande - someone like u (interlude) (official audio) - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande - 34+35 (Remix / Lyric Video) ft. Doja Cat, Megan Thee Stallion - Contained GENERIC phrase: Lyric Video.
&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande - excuse me, i love you (exclusive trailer) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande - 34+35 (official video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande - R.E.M. Fragrance Commercial (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande - six thirty (audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande - pov (audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande, The Weeknd - off the table (audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande, Doja Cat - motive (audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande - safety net (audio) ft. Ty Dolla $ign - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;THE PICTUREBOOKS - Here's To Magic feat. Dennis Lyxzen [Refused] (OFFICIAL VIDEO) - Contained not followed artist.
&lt;br&gt;Tori Kelly AND JoJo - (You Make Me Feel Like) A Natural Woman [Official Lyric Video] - Contained not followed artist.
&lt;br&gt;Behind the Scenes with Godsmack’s Unforgettable - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Godsmack - Unforgettable - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Godsmack Unforgettable 2020 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sully Erna AND The Scars Foundation Brings an Early Christmas for 3 Lucky Kids - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;"Under Your Scars" - Godsmack - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Scars Foundation Call to Action from Sully Erna - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Godsmack 2019 European Tour - Backstage Warm Ups - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Godsmack 2019 European Tour - Robbie's Worst Hits - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;"When Legends Rise" - Godsmack - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Godsmack - Unforgettable (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Godsmack - Take It To The Edge (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Godsmack - Every Part Of Me (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Godsmack - Under Your Scars (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;IHeartRadio LIVE with Godsmack ! - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;GODSMACK - When Legends Rise (Studio Update #1) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Katy Perry - Firework (Live from Celebrating America Inauguration Special) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Live.
&lt;br&gt;Katy Perry - Not the End of the World - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;I'll Be Home For Christmas / Cozy Little Christmas (From the Disney Holiday Singalong) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Katy Perry, Darius Rucker - Only Love (Live From The AMA’s /2020) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Katy Perry - Never Really Over/Not The End Of The World/Roar Medley (Live at T Mall Double 11 Gala) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Katy Perry, Tiësto, Aitana - Resilient (Tiësto Remix) #OpenToBetter Film - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Katy Perry, Tiësto - Resilient (ft. Aitana) [Tiësto Remix] – Visualizer - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Katy Perry - Teary Eyes (Behind The Smile) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Katy Perry - What Makes A Woman (The Smile Video Series) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Katy Perry - Resilient (The Smile Video Series) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Katy Perry - Champagne Problems (The Smile Video Series) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Katy Perry - Tucked (The Smile Video Series) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Katy Perry - Cry About It Later (The Smile Video Series) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Katy Perry - Harleys In Hawaii (The Smile Video Series) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Katy Perry - Never Really Over (The Smile Video Series) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Papa Roach - Broken As Me feat. Danny Worsnop of Asking Alexandria (Official Lyric Video) - Contained not followed artist.
&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish: "The World’s A Little Blurry" - Live Premiere Event - Contained GENERIC phrase: Live.
&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish - ilomilo (Live From The Film – Billie Eilish: The World’s A Little Blurry) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Live.
&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish - The Making of 'Therefore I Am' | Vevo Footnotes - Contained GENERIC phrase: Making of.
&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish: The World’s A Little Blurry - Official Trailer | Apple TV+ - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish - Therefore I Am (Live From The ARIAS) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish - everything i wanted (LIVE FROM THE STEVE JOBS THEATER) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish - Therefore I Am (Live from the American Music Awards / 2020) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish - Therefore I Am (Official Music Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;No Time To Die (Live from The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon from James Bond Day) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish - No Time To Die - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish: The World’s A Little Blurry – A Documentary Film - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish - my future (Live) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;REGISTER TO VOTE - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;THE PICTUREBOOKS - Here's To Magic feat. Dennis Lyxzen [Refused] (OFFICIAL VIDEO) - Contained not followed artist.
&lt;br&gt;Madonna - Living For Love (Live at the 2015 Grammy Awards) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Live.
&lt;br&gt;Madonna - Fever (Live from Saturday Night Live 1993) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Live.
&lt;br&gt;Madonna - World of Madame X - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Madonna - Hung Up (Tracy Young video remix edit) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Madonna - Hung Up (Live at the 2006 Grammy Awards) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Madonna - Hung Up (Live at the 2005 MTV EMAs) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Madonna - "Ray of Light - Words + Music" audio interview - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Madonna - Music [TV Edit] [Official HD Music Video] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;"Who's That Girl" (Official movie trailer) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Madonna - Bitch I'm Madonna (Live on The Tonight Show) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Madonna - Vogue (12" Remix video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Madonna - Hung Up (Live at Coachella 2006) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Madonna - Vogue (Live from the Sticky AND Sweet Tour) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Madonna - Vogue ('I'm Going To Tell You A Secret' documentary version) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;DIE ANTWOORD - ZEF GOEMA MEGAMIX ft Gqwa, Moonchild Sanelly, Slagysta AND Die Kaapse Klopse - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;¥o-Landi spitting over the Gqom part #BaitaJouSabela - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Die Antwoord - Future Baby (Official Music Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Die Antwoord #VeganAF - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Die Antwoord - LAMBO LIFE (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Die Antwoord - BANG ON EM (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Die Antwoord - HO$H HO$H HO$H feat Bobajan, Skelm (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Die Antwoord - WHEN THE SUN GOES OUT feat. Roger Ballen (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Die Antwoord - ZONKE BONKE feat. Bukhulubakhe, Gqwa! (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Die Antwoord - MY LIFE IS A PORNO feat. Smiley (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Die Antwoord - DA GODZ MUS B KRAZY (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Die Antwoord - FUTURE BABY (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;DIE ANTWOORD - HOUSE OF ZEF - MEGAMIX9000 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Die Antwoord - DON'T SLEEP (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Die Antwoord - OPEN THE DOOR feat. Panther Modern (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;MUDBANGERS BALL - LIVE (CODE ORANGE) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;ECT2020: Yipes AND Matrix Watch Trivium – Catastrophist - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;ECT2020: Yipes AND Matrix Watch Code Orange – Sulfur Surrounding - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;ECT2020: Yipes AND Matrix Watch Coheed AND Cambria – Jessie's Girl 2 (feat. Rick Springfield) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;ECT2020: Yipes AND Matrix Watch Gojira – Silvera - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;ECT2020: Yipes AND Matrix Watch Turnstile – Real Thing - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;How To Do An Infinite by Chris Matrix (Magneto ROM) #ECT2020 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Roadrunner Records X ASTRO Warzone Charity Challenge - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;PlayOn Fest (Music is NOT Cancelled) LIVE Fri April 24 @ 12PM EST - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Trivium Music Video QANDA - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Matty Matheson: A Cookbook comes to Vinyl - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Type O Negative Interview: Touring with Nine Inch Nails - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;East Coast Throwdown 2018 Recap - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;East Coast Throwdown - LI Joe - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;East Coast Throwdown - Alex Smith - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rammstein - Herzeleid (XXV Anniversary Edition - Remastered) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;NORTH AMERICA STADIUM TOUR RESCHEDULED TO 2021! - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;EUROPE STADIUM TOUR RESCHEDULED TO 2021! - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rammstein - Making Of Album-Photosession (Official) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rammstein - Europe Stadium Tour (Time Lapse) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rammstein Zeppelin - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rammstein - Ausländer (Official Making Of) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rammstein App (Official) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rammstein - Radio (Official Making Of) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rammstein - Ausländer (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rammstein - Stripped (Official Making Of) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rammstein - Stripped (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rammstein - Radio (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;HALLOMANN - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;TATTOO - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - Realize (Official Video Behind the Scenes) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Behind the scenes.
&lt;br&gt;#PWRUP THE WORLD 🇵🇱 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - Demon Fire (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - DEMON FIRE (OFFICIAL VIDEO TRAILER) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - DEMON FIRE (FROM FORTNITE NEXUS WAR FINALE) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;#PWRUP - A MESSAGE FROM BRIAN - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;#PWRUP BTS 4 - ANGUS AND BRIAN ON REALIZE - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - Demon Fire (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - Money Shot (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - Code Red (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - Kick You When You're Down (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - No Man's Land (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - Wild Reputation (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Static-X Official 20th Anniversary Wisconsin Death Trip World Tour PROMO - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Wisconsin Death Trip 20th Anniversary Tour - Australia - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Wisconsin Death Trip 20 Year Anniversary Tour / Static-X / Devil Driver / Dope / Wayne Memorial - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Eminem - Godzilla (Lyric Video) ft. Juice WRLD - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Premonition - Intro [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Unaccommodating (feat. Young M.A) [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;You Gon' Learn (feat. Royce Da 5'9" AND White Gold) [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;In Too Deep [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Those Kinda Nights (feat. Ed Sheeran) [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Godzilla (feat. Juice WRLD) [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Darkness [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Leaving Heaven (feat. Skylar Grey) [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Yah Yah (feat. Royce Da 5'9", Black Thought, Q-Tip AND Denaun) [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Stepdad [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Marsh [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Never Love Again [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Lock It Up (feat. Anderson .Paak) [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - Restrung Live - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - Parade of the Dead (Live Concert 2010) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - I'm Good? (Official Lyrics Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - The Great Expanse World Tour (North America Tour Diary) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - ‘The Great Expanse’ World Tour Europe AND UK Part 6 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - ‘The Great Expanse’ World Tour Europe AND UK Part 5 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - ‘The Great Expanse’ World Tour Europe AND UK Part 4 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - The Great Expanse’ World Tour Europe AND UK Part 3 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - ‘The Great Expanse’ World Tour Europe AND UK Part 2 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - ‘The Great Expanse’ World Tour Europe AND UK Pt. 1 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - Biggest Headline Show! Sydney Australia, Qudas Bank Arena - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - Brisbane Australia, Riverstage Night 2 (The Great Expanse World Tour) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - Brisbane Australia, Riverstage Night 1 (The Great Expanse World Tour) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - Adelaide Australia, AEC (The Great Expanse World Tour) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - Melbourne Australia, Rod Laver Arena Round 2 (The Great Expanse World Tour) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Foo Fighters - Making A Fire (Live) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Live.
&lt;br&gt;Foo Fighters - Making A Fire (Visualizer) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Visualizer.
&lt;br&gt;Foo Fighters - Medicine At Midnight (Visualizer) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Visualizer.
&lt;br&gt;Foo Fighters - Love Dies Young (Visualizer) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Visualizer.
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys "Next Girl" Remastered 10th Anniversary Edition [Official Audio] - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys "Ten Cent Pistol" Remastered 10th Anniversary Edition [Official Audio] - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys "She's Long Gone" Remastered 10th Anniversary Edition [Official Audio] - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys "Black Mud Part II" Remastered 10th Anniversary Edition [Official Audio] - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys "The Only One" Remastered 10th Anniversary Edition [Official Audio] - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys "Chop and Change" Remastered 10th Anniversary Edition [Official Audio] - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys "Keep My Name Outta Your Mouth" Remastered 10th Anniversary Edition [Official Audio] - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys "Never Gonna Give You Up" Remastered 10th Anniversary Edition [Official Audio] - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys "Sinister Kid" Remastered 10th Anniversary Edition [Official Audio] - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys "Unknown Brother" Remastered 10th Anniversary Edition [Official Audio] - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys "Everlasting Light" Remastered 10th Anniversary Edition [Official Audio] - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys "Howlin' for You" Remastered 10th Anniversary Edition [Official Audio] - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys "Black Mud" Remastered 10th Anniversary Edition [Official Audio] - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys "I'm Not the One" Remastered 10th Anniversary Edition [Official Audio] - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;LOVEYOURLIFE #2020 - video lookbook - Contained not followed artist.

&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
<dc:creator> &lt;a&gt;Bednar&lt;/a&gt;</dc:creator>
</item>
</rdf:RDF>