<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<rdf:RDF
 xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#"
 xmlns="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/"
 xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
 xmlns:taxo="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/taxonomy/"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:syn="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
 xmlns:admin="http://webns.net/mvcb/"
>
<channel rdf:about="http://spotify.com/">
<title>Spotify new releases</title>
<link>http://spotify.com/</link>
<description rdf:parseType="Literal">Releases of followed artists on Spotify</description>
<dc:language>en-us</dc:language>
<dc:date>2018-03-07T20:30:00-05:00</dc:date>
<dc:publisher>help@spotify.com</dc:publisher>
<dc:subject>Music</dc:subject>
<syn:updateBase>1901-01-01T00:00+00:00</syn:updateBase>
<syn:updateFrequency>1</syn:updateFrequency>
<syn:updatePeriod>daily</syn:updatePeriod>
<items>
 <rdf:Seq>
<rdf:li rdf:resource="http://spotify.com"/></rdf:Seq>
</items>
<image rdf:resource="https://www.scdn.co/i/_global/favicon.png" />
</channel>
<image rdf:about="https://www.scdn.co/i/_global/favicon.png">
<title>Spotify releases</title>
<url>https://www.scdn.co/i/_global/favicon.png</url>
<link>http://spotify.com</link>
</image><item rdf:about="http://spotify.com">
<title>2019-10-30 08:24 YouTube newest rejects</title>
<link>http://spotify.com</link>
<description rdf:parseType="Literal">&lt;p&gt;New releases:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - Europe AND UK 2020 Tour Announce - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - Knotfest Roadshow (Tour Update) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Alexa: Play 'We Are Not Your Kind' by Slipknot (Amazon Music) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - Death Because of Death (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - Insert Coin (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - Red Flag (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - Not Long For This World (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - My Pain (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - A Liar's Funeral (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - Orphan (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - What's Next (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - Nero Forte (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - Critical Darling (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - Spiders (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slipknot - Birth Of The Cruel (Vertical Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - "False God" (Live on Saturday Night Live / 2019) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Live.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - "Lover" (Live on Saturday Night Live / 2019) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Live.
&lt;br&gt;Lover Album Photoshoot: Behind The Scenes - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - The Man (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - Daylight (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - I Forgot That You Existed (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - Cruel Summer (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - It’s Nice To Have A Friend (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - Soon You’ll Get Better (Official Audio) ft. Dixie Chicks - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - Miss Americana AND The Heartbreak Prince (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - Death By A Thousand Cuts (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - London Boy (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - Cornelia Street (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - Paper Rings (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift - False God (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;MICAWBER WELCOME HOME (KING DIAMOND COVER) - Contained not followed artist.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic - Club Majesty Tour 2019/2020 - Contained GENERIC phrase: Tour.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic - Stop Movin' (Live @ Skärgårdsfest) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Live.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic - What a summer! Can't wait to kick off the Club Majesty European Tour in October! - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic - Like A Lover (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic - Anna-Leigh (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic - Boomerang (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic - Fireman AND Dancer (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic Tour Postmonement 2019 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic 10 Years Anniversary Movie (Part 6) - Highlights - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic 10 Years Anniversary Movie (Part 5) - Weekend Man - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic 10 Years Anniversary Movie (Part 4) - The Nosebreakers - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic 10 Years Anniversary Movie (Part 3) - Save The Nation - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic 10 Years Anniversary Movie (Part 2) - We Are The Royal - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic 10 Years Anniversary Movie (Part 1) - The Beginning - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Royal Republic AND The Nosebreakers - Let Your Hair Down (Live At The Gloria Theater) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mario Duplantier - Drum solo Bloodstock 2018 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;GOJIRA - Pol'And'Rock Festival 2018 [LIVE] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;GOJIRA - Bloodstock 2018 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;GOJIRA - Into The Grave Festival 2018 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;GOJIRA - Brutal Assault 2018 (Czech Republic) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Gojira - Lokerse Feesten (Belgium) 2018 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;GOJIRA - Wacken Open Air 2018 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;GOJIRA - POL'AND ROCK 2018 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Gojira - Global Warming [Live at the Silver Cord Studio May 2018] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;GOJIRA - Silvera live - Hellfest 2016 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Gojira - Toxic Garbage Island ( Live Hellfest 2016) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;THE MAGMA TOUR US - Fall 2017 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Magma Tour - US October 2017 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Gojira - North America - August 2017 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Gojira Memories - Europe Sommer 2017 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Post Malone AND Red Hot Chili Peppers - Stay / Rockstar / Dark Necessities (LIVE at the 61st GRAMMYs) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Flea On RHCP Fans [The Getaway Track-By-Track Commentary] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Flea On His Preshow Rituals  [The Getaway Track-By-Track Commentary] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Goodbye Angels [OFFICIAL VIDEO] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Chad On His Preshow Rituals [The Getaway Track-By-Track Commentary] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Flea on Free Time Between Albums [The Getaway Track-By-Track Commentary] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Anthony on Relationship with Fans [The Getaway Track-By-Track Commentary] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Josh's Preshow Rituals [The Getaway Track-By-Track Commentary] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Anthony On Working With Brian Burton [The Getaway Track-By-Track Commentary] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Anthony's Preshow Rituals [The Getaway Track-By-Track Commentary] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Sick Love [OFFICIAL VIDEO] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Anthony Explains the Album Title [The Getaway Track-By-Track Commentary] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Flea on the Energy of the Live Shows [The Getaway Track-By-Track Commentary] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - The Getaway [Live Download from Munich, Germany 11.01.16] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Red Hot Chili Peppers - Nobody Weird Like Me [Live Download from Munich, Germany 11.01.16] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak - Bronsegud [OFFICIAL VIDEO] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak - Svartmesse [OFFICIAL VIDEO] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak - Nattesferd [OFFICIAL VIDEO] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak - Berserkr (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak - Heksebrann (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak - Dendrofil for Yggdrasil (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak - Svartmesse (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak - Nekrodamus (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak - Ondskapens Galakse (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak - Nattesferd (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak - 1985 [OFFICIAL VIDEO] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak - Nattesferd (Teaser) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak - UK SHOWS // NOVEMBER 2015 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak are currently on tour with Slayer, and will be playing headline shows in: - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Kvelertak - Evig Vandrar [OFFICIAL VIDEO] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ellie Goulding - Hate Me (with Juice WRLD) [R3HAB Remix] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ellie Goulding, Juice WRLD - Hate Me (Vertical Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ellie Goulding, Juice WRLD - Hate Me - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ellie Goulding, Juice WRLD - Hate Me (Trailer) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ellie Goulding AND Juice WRLD - Hate Me (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ellie Goulding - Sixteen (Acoustic) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ellie Goulding - Sixteen (Don Diablo Remix) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ellie Goulding - Sixteen - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ellie Goulding - Sixteen (Lyric Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ellie Goulding - Flux - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ellie Goulding (with Diplo) (Ft. Swae Lee) - Close To Me CID Remix - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ellie Goulding (with Diplo) (Ft. Swae Lee) - Close To Me Felix Cartal Remix - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ellie Goulding, Diplo, Swae Lee - Close To Me (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit - Toazted Interview 1998 (part 2) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit - Toazted Interview 1998 (part 1) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit - Toazted Interview 1998 (part 3) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit - Toazted Interview 1998 (part 4) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Endless Slaughter (Official Visual 2014) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;LIGHTZ (Official Video) - Limp Bizkit - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit "Behind Blue Eyes" - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit "Boiler" - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit "Break Stuff" - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit "Eat You Alive" - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit "My Way" - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit "Faith" REMIX - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit - Ready To Go (Official Music Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit - Lightz - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Limp Bizkit - Ready To Go ft. Lil Wayne (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Embryo live February 2017 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Embryo feat. Deobrat and Prashant Mishra 2017 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Embryo - Mal Waldron -  Memorial Concert - Left Alone - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Embryo in the Seventies, Vlotho 78 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Embryo in the Seventies, Feature, WDR 1980 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Embryo and Friends, La Pirata, Llanca, Spain, 21.02.2016 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Embryo + Wieland Rehm - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Embryo live, Embryokeller München 09.Januar 2016 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Embryo and Mal Waldron, TU Mensa Munich,  29. Nov. 1990 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;ADM - Free-Haven - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mal Waldron AND Embryo, 20 Jahrfeier, Part I - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mal Waldron AND Embryo, 20 Jahrfeier, Part II - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Embryo - Agnessession - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Roman Bunka AND Christian Burchard - Sunsong - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Roman Bunka AND Christian Burchard - Moll - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - The Making of Crack The Skye | Part 6 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - Stairway to Heaven [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - Stairway to Heaven (Live) [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - The Making of Crack The Skye | Part 5 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - The Making of Crack The Skye | Part 4 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - The Making of Crack The Skye | Part 3 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - The Making of Crack The Skye | Part 2 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - The Last Baron [Official Visualizer] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - Ghost of Karelia [Official Visualizer] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - Divinations [Official Visualizer] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - Crack The Skye [Official Visualizer] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - Quintessence [Official Visualizer] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - Oblivion [Official Visualizer] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - The Czar [Official Visualizer] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Mastodon - The Making of Crack The Skye | Part 1 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;OUR HAUS. YOUR RULES. | HAUS LABORATORIES - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga, Bradley Cooper - Shallow (From A Star Is Born/Live From The Oscars) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;ENIGMA - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga - Always Remember Us This Way (From A Star Is Born Soundtrack) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga, Bradley Cooper - I'll Never Love Again - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga - Look What I Found (A Star Is Born) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Bradley Cooper - Maybe It's Time (From A Star Is Born Soundtrack/ Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga - Is That Alright? (From A Star Is Born Soundtrack/Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga - I'll Never Love Again (From A Star Is Born Soundtrack/ Extended Version/Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga, Bradley Cooper - Shallow (A Star Is Born) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga - Your Song (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga - Joanne (Where Do You Think You’re Goin’?) (Piano Version) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Happy Birthday Sonja - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;LADY GAGA - JOANNE WORLD TOUR (Film 1) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - Hurts 2B Human (Kat Krazy Remix (Audio)) ft. Khalid - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - Hurts 2B Human (FTampa Remix (Audio)) ft. Khalid - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - Hurts 2B Human (Alex Ghenea Remix (Audio)) ft. Khalid - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - Hurts 2B Human (Midnight Kids Remix (Audio)) ft. Khalid - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - Hurts 2B Human (Frank Pole Remix (Audio)) ft. Khalid - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - Hurts 2B Human feat. Khalid - Behind The Scenes - Contained GENERIC phrase: Behind the scenes.
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - Can We Pretend (Animated Video) ft. Cash Cash - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - Can We Pretend (Sigala Remix (Audio)) ft. Cash Cash - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - 90 Days (Official Video) ft. Wrabel - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - Walk Me Home (Dinaire+Bissen Remix (Audio)) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - Walk Me Home (R3HAB Extended Mix (Audio)) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - Walk Me Home (Until Dawn Remix (Audio)) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;P!nk VS Sink The Pink in Walk Me Home - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;P!nk - Circle Game (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Nocny Kochanek - SKARfest 2019 - zapowiedź koncertu w Skarżysku-Kamiennej - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Nocny Kochanek - Tribjut / Andrzela - Record Store Day 2019 (Akustycznie) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Nocny Kochanek - Trasa w Ciemność / Record Store Day 2019 - Raport z Poznania - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Nocny Kochanek - Koń na Białym Rycerzu (Oficjalny Teledysk) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Nocny Kochanek - Trasa w Ciemność - Zapowiedź koncertu w Pile - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Nocny Kochanek - Trasa w Ciemność - Zapowiedź koncertu w Bydgoszczy - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Nocny Kochanek - Trasa w Ciemność - Zapowiedź koncertu w Gdyni - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;01. Nocny Kochanek - Randka w Ciemno (Oficjalny Odsłuch Albumu) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;02. Nocny Kochanek - Dr O. Ngal  (Oficjalny Odsłuch Albumu) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;03. Nocny Kochanek - Al Dente (Oficjalny Odsłuch Albumu) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;04. Nocny Kochanek -  Pijany Mistrz (Oficjalny Odsłuch Albumu) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;05. Nocny Kochanek - Koń Na Białym Rycerzu (Oficjalny Odsłuch Albumu) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;06. Nocny Kochanek -  Tirowiec  (Oficjalny Odsłuch Albumu) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;07. Nocny Kochanek -  Andrzela  (Oficjalny Odsłuch Albumu) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Alexa, play me some hot garbage (this actually works) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Uniform On | The Unauthorized Bash Brothers Experience - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Oakland Nights (feat. Sia) | The Unauthorized Bash Brothers Experience - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Lil' Tour Announcement - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;OSCAR SONG DEMO - "Why Not Me?" - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Jack Sparrow Unplugged (from Michael Bolton's Netflix Special) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Old Time Rock N Roll (from Netflix's Michael Bolton's Big Sexy Valentine's Day Special) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Natalie's Rap 2.0 (Uncensored Version) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;I'm On A Boat - Classroom Instruments w Jimmy Fallon AND The Roots - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Shy Ronnie (ft. Rihanna) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;conner4real Radio Freestyle - Big Boy (92.3) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Lazy Sunday Live w/ The Roots - Late Night w Jimmy Fallon - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;conner4real - "F**k Off" (Popstar Deleted Scene/Song) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;I'm A Weirdo - Conner4real One-Take Music Video - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Christina Aguilera - Haunted Heart (Lyric Video) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Lyric Video.
&lt;br&gt;Christina Aguilera: The Xperience - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Christina Aguilera - Like I Do (Lyric Video) ft. GoldLink - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Christina Aguilera - Fall In Line feat. Demi Lovato - Behind The Scenes - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Christina Aguilera - Like I Do (Audio) ft. GoldLink - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Christina Aguilera - Fall In Line (Official Video) ft. Demi Lovato - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Christina Aguilera ft. Demi Lovato - Fall In Line (Official Lyric Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Christina Aguilera - Twice (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Where’s Maria? (Liberation by Christina Aguilera) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Christina Aguilera - Accelerate (Official Video) ft. Ty Dolla $ign, 2 Chainz - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Christina Aguilera - Ven Conmigo (Solamente Tú) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Christina Aguilera - Telepathy (feat. Nile Rodgers) [Fan Video] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Christina Aguilera - Change (Lyric Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine - Znak 🔑 (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Przebój Rocku Antyradia - "Jak Ci Powiedzieć?"🎸 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine - Błyski ⚡ (Lyric Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine - Jak Ci Powiedzieć? 🎱 (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine - Odchodząc 🏁 (Republika Cover) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine - Pretending 🔮 (Official Live Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine - Neverland 🍂 (Official Live Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine - Secret Self 🎭 (Live ❣ WOŚP ❣ Sanok) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine - Dicegame 🎲(Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine - Broken 🖤 (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine - Stop Me💸(Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine - Secret Self 🎭(Acoustic Czwórka) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine #Stop Me (Trailer) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine Photoshoot 🎸 (Thug Life) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hurrockaine - Peter Pan (Live Session) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Proseko - Wsiadam do auta (prod. megot) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;RAU_PERFORMANCE - ODKRYJ W SOBIE LATO. - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;RAU_PERFORMANCE - FYI (INTRO) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;RAU_PERFORMANCE - NIKT W POLSCE. - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;RAU_PERFORMANCE - ŚCIANA - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;RAU_PERFORMANCE - DOJADAMY (FT. KSIĄŻE KAPOTA, FROSTI REGE, ŻYTO) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;RAU_PERFORMANCE - MISTRZ_SZTUKI. - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;EN2AK FT. RAU - GUMOWA KACZKA [POLAKPOTRAFI.PL] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;RAU_PERFORMANCE - NIE DZWOŃ, NIE PISZ. - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;🍄 ŚMIESZNY GRZYB 🍄 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;BAASCH - KIND OF COMA (RAU REMIX) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;RAU ♫ █▬█ █ ▀█▀ ♫ 🍷 W!NKO 🍷 ♫ █▬█ █ ▀█▀ ♫ RAU - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;BIAŁAS AND LANEK -  SIMIA (RAU REMIX) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;RAU -  BALLSOUT - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;RAU -  DZIŚ NIE - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Marilyn Manson - Cry Little Sister - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Marilyn Manson - Cry Little Sister - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Marilyn Manson AND Rob Zombie Discuss The First Time They Heard Each Other's Music - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Twins of Evil Tour – The Second Coming - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Marilyn Manson - Tattooed In Reverse (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Marilyn Manson - KILL4ME (Music Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;MARILYN MANSON - Revelation #12 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;MARILYN MANSON - Tattooed In Reverse - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;MARILYN MANSON - Saturnalia - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;MARILYN MANSON - JE$U$ CRI$I$ - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;MARILYN MANSON - Blood Honey - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;MARILYN MANSON - Heaven Upside Down - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;MARILYN MANSON - KILL4ME - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;MARILYN MANSON - Threats of Romance - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie’s Three From Hell - Teaser Trailer - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Twins of Evil - Hell Never Dies Tour 2019 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie AND Marilyn Manson Discuss The First Time They Heard Each Other's Music - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Twins of Evil Tour – The Second Coming - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie - ASTRO-CREEP: 2000 LIVE - OUT NOW! - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie - Vinyl Catalog - Available Now! - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie Career Vinyl Box - OUT NOW! - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie Career Vinyl Box Set - OUT NOW! - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie - ASTRO-CREEP: 2000 LIVE - Available March 30 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie - Vinyl Catalog - Available March 30 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie Career Vinyl Box - Available March 30 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie Career Vinyl Box Set - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie - Get Your Boots On! That's The End Of Rock And Roll! - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie - The Hideous Exhibitions Of A Dedicated Gore Whore - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rob Zombie - Medication For The Melancholy - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - Desert Queen - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - Chaos Royale - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - Chaos Royale (Lyric) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - 24/7 (Video Commentary) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - Fight Song - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - Hearts of Cold - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - End Of The Line - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - End Of The Line (Lyric video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - 24/7 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - Outrage - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - Rock 'N' Roll (Motörhead Cover) ft. Doro - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - One Out of Ten - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - On Parole - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Sister Sin - Sound of the Underground - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Korn x Breaking Benjamin 🔲 Winter 2020 North American Tour - Contained GENERIC phrase: Tour.
&lt;br&gt;Korn - You'll Never Find Me (Official Live Video) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Live.
&lt;br&gt;Korn - H@rd3r (Official Audio) - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;Korn - This Loss (Official Audio) - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;Korn - Surrender To Failure (Official Audio) - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;Korn - The Darkness is Revealing (Official Audio) - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;Korn - Gravity Of Discomfort (Official Audio) - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;Korn - The Ringmaster (Official Audio) - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;Korn - Finally Free (Official Audio) - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;Korn - The Seduction Of Indulgence (Official Audio) - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;Korn - Idiosyncracy (Official Audio) - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;Korn - The End Begins (Official Audio) - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;Korn - Can You Hear Me (Official Visualizer) / The Nothing Podcast (Official Trailer) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Visualizer.
&lt;br&gt;Korn - Cold (Official Visualizer) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Korn - You'll Never Find Me (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;CKY - Bite It You Scum (Official Music Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;CKY - Wiping Off The Dead - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;CKY - Head For A Breakdown (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;CKY - Replaceable - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;CKY - Days Of Self Destruction - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;CKY - Afterworld (Behind The Scenes) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;CKY - Flesh Into Gear - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;CKY - Familiar Realm - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;CKY - Attached At The Hip (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;CKY - Flesh Into Gear (Blurred Version) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Glitch Mob - Alchemy Tour Recap [Part 3] - Contained GENERIC phrase: Tour.
&lt;br&gt;The Glitch Mob AND LICK - 'System Bleed' Live at The Gorge - Contained GENERIC phrase: Live.
&lt;br&gt;The Glitch Mob - Alchemy Tour Recap [Part 2] - Contained GENERIC phrase: Tour.
&lt;br&gt;The Glitch Mob - Alchemy Tour Recap - Contained GENERIC phrase: Tour.
&lt;br&gt;The Glitch Mob at Exchange LA | 2.14.19 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Glitch Mob - I Could Be Anything (ft. Elohim) [Hallucinogenius Remix] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Glitch Mob - I Could Be Anything (ft. Elohim) [Rezz Remix] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Glitch Mob - Keep on Breathing (ft. Tula) [Kmln Remix] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Glitch Mob - Go Light [29 Palms Remix] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Glitch Mob - Take Me With You (ft. Arama) [Rob Simonsen Remix] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Glitch Mob - Way Out Is In [Bluetech Remix] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Glitch Mob - How Could This Be Wrong (ft. Tula) [Tsuruda Remix] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Glitch Mob - Interbeing [Huxley Anne Remix] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Steel Panther -"All I Wanna Do Is Fuck (Myself Tonight)": Behind the Scenes (Episode #4) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Behind the scenes.
&lt;br&gt;Steel Panther -"All I Wanna Do Is Fuck (Myself Tonight)": Behind the Scenes (Episode #3) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Behind the scenes.
&lt;br&gt;Steel Panther -"All I Wanna Do Is Fuck (Myself Tonight)": Behind the Scenes (Episode #2) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Behind the scenes.
&lt;br&gt;Steel Panther -"All I Wanna Do Is Fuck (Myself Tonight)": Behind the Scenes (Episode #1) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Steel Panther TV presents: "The World's Greatest Discoveries: Part Two - Fire" - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Steel Panther TV presents: "The World's Greatest Discoveries: Part One - Electricity" - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slash ft Myles Kennedy AND The Conspirators - Shadow Life (Living The Dream) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slash Ft. Myles Kennedy AND The Conspirators - Living The Dream Tour (ORDER NOW) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slash ft. Myles Kennedy AND The Conspirators – Living The Dream Tour Teaser (Order Now) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slash ft. Myles Kennedy AND The Conspirators – Anastasia (Living The Dream Tour) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slash ft. Myles Kennedy AND The Conspirators: Behind-the-Scenes at Download Festival 2019 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slash ft. Myles Kennedy AND The Conspirators - "Boulevard of Broken Hearts" Official Music Video - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slash ft. Myles Kennedy AND The Conspirators – Euro Tour 2019: Behind-the-Scenes in Berlin - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slash ft. Myles Kennedy AND The Conspirators – Euro Tour 2019: Behind-the-Scenes in Paris - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slash ft. Myles Kennedy AND The Conspirators – Euro Tour 2019: Behind-the-Scenes in Lodz - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Slash ft  Myles Kennedy AND The Conspirators - "Mind Your Manners" Official Music Video - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;SLASH FT. MYLES KENNEDY AND THE CONSPIRATORS - "Driving Rain" Official Music Video - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;SLASH FT. MYLES KENNEDY AND THE CONSPIRATORS - "The Great Pretender" Full Song Static Video - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;SLASH FT. MYLES KENNEDY AND THE CONSPIRATORS - "Boulevard of Broken Hearts" Full Song Static Video - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;SLASH FT. MYLES KENNEDY AND THE CONSPIRATORS - "Read Between The Lines" Full Song Static Video - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge - "Take The Crown" (OFFICIAL VIDEO) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge: "Pay No Mind" (OFFICIAL) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge: Open Your Eyes (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge - Wouldn't You Rather (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;"Words Darker Than Their Wings"  Alter Bridge: Orchestra Only (OFFICIAL VIDEO) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge:  "The End Is Here"  Live At The Royal Albert Hall (OFFICIAL VIDEO) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge:  "Words Darker Than Their Wings"  Live At The Royal Albert Hall (OFFICIAL VIDEO) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge: Live At The Royal Albert Hall (OFFICIAL TRAILER) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge:  "Addicted To Pain" Live At The Royal Albert Hall (OFFICIAL VIDEO) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Alter Bridge - Live At The Royal Albert Hall Featuring The Parallax Orchestra (OFFICIAL TEASER) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - Always There (Audio) - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - The March Of The Peaceful Army begins - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - Highway Tune (Live) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - Safari Song (Live) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - Edge Of Darkness (Live) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - You’re The One (Live on SNL / 2019) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - Black Smoke Rising (Live on SNL / 2019) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - You're The One (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - Anthem Of The Peaceful Army Animation Clip - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - The New Day (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - The Cold Wind (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - Mountain of the Sun (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - Brave New World (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - Age of Man (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Greta Van Fleet - Lover, Leaver (Taker, Believer) (Live) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System Of A Down - Bounce (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System of a Down - Toazted Interview 2002 (Daron, part 1) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System of a Down - Toazted Interview 2002 (Daron, part 2) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System of a Down - Toazted Interview 2002 (Daron, part 3) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System of a Down - Toazted Interview 2002 (Daron, part 4) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System of a Down - Toazted Interview 2001 (Shavo, part 3) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System of a Down - Toazted Interview 2001 (Shavo, part 1) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System of a Down - Toazted Interview 2001 (Shavo, part 2) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System of a Down - Toazted Interview 2001 (whole band, part 1) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System of a Down - Toazted Interview 2001 (whole band, part 3) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System of a Down - Toazted Interview 2001 (whole band, part 2) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System Of A Down - Lonely Day (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System Of A Down - Aerials (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System Of A Down - B.Y.O.B. (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;System Of A Down - Question! (Official Concept Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;POWERMAN 5000 West Coast Death Ray Fun Time Invasion Tour - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;POWERMAN 5000 - Footsteps and Voices - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Powerman 5000 - David Fucking Bowie - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;POWERMAN 5000 - "Cult Leader" - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Powerman 5000 - Sid Vicious in a Dress - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;POWERMAN 5000 - "Sid Vicious In A Dress" (audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;POWERMAN 5000 - "Invade Destroy Repeat" (official video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Powerman 5000 - How To Be A Human - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Powerman 5000 - How To Be A Human (Lyric Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Powerman 5000 - Bombshell - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Powerman 5000 - Tokyo Vigilante #1 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Powerman 5000 - Nobody's Real (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Powerman 5000 - Super Villain - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Powerman 5000 - Free - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Powerman 5000 - Supernova Goes Pop - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea - Behind The Scenes: Iggy Azalea "In My Defense" Album Release Week - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea - Thanks I Get (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea - Comme Des Garcons (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea - Pussy Pop (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea - Spend It (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea - Hoemita (Audio) ft. Lil Yachty - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea - Freak Of The Week (Audio) ft. Juicy J - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea - Big Bag (Audio) ft. Stini - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea - Clap Back (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea - F*ck It Up (Official Music Video) ft. Kash Doll - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea - Started (Official Music Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea - Sally Walker (Official Music Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea - Kream ft. Tyga - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea - Savior ft. Quavo - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Iggy Azalea - Savior ft. Quavo (Lyric Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Don’t Call Me Angel (Charlie’s Angels) (Lyric Video) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Lyric Video.
&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande - Lollapalooza (recap) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande AND Social House - boyfriend (behind the scenes) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande AND Social House - boyfriend (behind the scenes montage) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande AND Social House - boyfriend (lyric video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande AND Social House - boyfriend (AUDIO) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande, Social House - boyfriend - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande - 7 rings (Live From The Billboard Music Awards / 2019) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande and Victoria Monét - MONOPOLY - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande - ghostin (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande - in my head (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;SWALLOW THE SUN - Stone Wings (Live at John Smith Festival) - Contained not followed artist.
&lt;br&gt;Why Don't We - Mad At You [Official Audio] - Contained not followed artist.
&lt;br&gt;"Under Your Scars" - Godsmack - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Scars Foundation Call to Action from Sully Erna - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Godsmack 2019 European Tour - Backstage Warm Ups - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Godsmack 2019 European Tour - Robbie's Worst Hits - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;"When Legends Rise" - Godsmack - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Godsmack - Unforgettable (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Godsmack - Take It To The Edge (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Godsmack - Every Part Of Me (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Godsmack - Under Your Scars (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;IHeartRadio LIVE with Godsmack ! - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;GODSMACK - When Legends Rise (Studio Update #1) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Godsmack - When Legends Rise (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Godsmack - Bulletproof (Director's Cut) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Bulletproof - Official Trailer - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Godsmack - Bulletproof (Official Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Katy Perry - Small Talk (Live On The Ellen Show) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Live.
&lt;br&gt;Katy Perry - Making of "Small Talk" / Episode #4 - Contained GENERIC phrase: Making of.
&lt;br&gt;Katy Perry - Making of "Small Talk" / Episode #3 - Contained GENERIC phrase: Making of.
&lt;br&gt;Katy Perry - Small Talk (Official) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Katy Perry - Making of "Small Talk" / Episode #2 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Katy Perry - Making of "Small Talk" / Episode #1 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Katy Perry - Small Talk (Lyric Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Katy Perry - Never Really Over (Lyric Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Katy Perry - Never Really Over (Vertical Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Katy Perry - Making Of “Never Really Over” Music Video - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Katy Perry “Never Really Over” YouTube Space Premiere Event - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Katy Perry - Never Really Over (Official) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Papa Roach - Feel Like Home (Acoustic) - Contained not followed artist.
&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish - i love you (Live From Saturday Night Live) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Live.
&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish - bad guy (Live From Saturday Night Live) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Live.
&lt;br&gt;WHERE DO WE GO? WORLD TOUR - Contained GENERIC phrase: Tour.
&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish - bad guy (Vertical Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish - i love you (Live At The Greek Theatre) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish - bad guy (with Justin Bieber) [Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish - A Snippet into Billie's Mind (Artist Spotlight Stories) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish - bad guy (Live From Jimmy Kimmel Live!/2019) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish - wish you were gay (Live) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish - you should see me in a crown (Official Video By Takashi Murakami) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;A Snippet into Billie's Mind - xanny - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish - when the party’s over (Live From The Ellen Show/2019) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish - bury a friend (Live From Jimmy Kimmel Live!/2019) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;SWALLOW THE SUN - Stone Wings (Live at John Smith Festival) - Contained not followed artist.
&lt;br&gt;Madonna - Crave (Twisted Dee AND Diego Fernandez Remix/Audio) ft. Swae Lee - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;Madonna - Crave (Otto Benson Remix/Audio) ft. Swae Lee - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;Madonna - Crave (Tracy Young Dangerous Radio Edit/Audio) ft. Swae Lee - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;Madonna - Crave (Benny Benassi AND BB Team Radio Edit/Audio) ft. Swae Lee - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;Madonna - Crave (RNG Club Remix/Audio) ft. Swae Lee - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;Madonna - Crave (Tracy Young Dangerous Remix/Audio) ft. Swae Lee - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;Madonna - Crave (Benny Benassi AND BB Team Extended Remix/Audio) ft. Swae Lee - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;Madonna - Crave (Dan De Leon AND Anthony Griego Remix/Audio) ft. Swae Lee - Contained GENERIC phrase: (Audio).
&lt;br&gt;Madonna - Batuka - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Madonna - God Control (Official Music Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Madonna - Dark Ballet (Official Music Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Madonna, Swae Lee - Crave - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Madonna, Quavo - Eurovision Song Contest 2019 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Madonna, Quavo - Future (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Madonna, Swae Lee - Crave (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;ZEF TV ~ Episode 2: 'May The Bridges I Burn Light The Way' - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;ZEF TV PUBLIC SERVICE ANNOUNCEMENT - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;ZEF TV ~ Episode 1: 'Sometimes I Know I Can Feel Like I’m A Fucking Killer' - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;ASK NO QUESTIONS - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;SUFFER - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;ONLY GOD - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;ANGEL - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;KILLER - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;LOADED PISTOL - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Matty Matheson: A Cookbook comes to Vinyl - Contained not followed artist.
&lt;br&gt;Rammstein Europe Stadium Tour 2020 (On Sale Now!) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rammstein Tour 2020 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rammstein App (Official) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rammstein - Radio (Official Making Of) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rammstein Europe Stadium Tour 2020 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rammstein - Ausländer (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rammstein - Stripped (Official Making Of) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rammstein - Stripped (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rammstein - Radio (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;HALLOMANN - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;TATTOO - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Rammstein - New Album - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;WEIT WEG - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;DIAMANT - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;WAS ICH LIEBE - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - Whole Lotta Rosie (from Countdown, 1979) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - Love Hungry Man (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - Night Prowler (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - Beating Around the Bush (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - Roadmap of Highway to Hell (from the film The Story of Back In Black) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - Get It Hot (Audio) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - The Jack (from Countdown, 1979) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - Highway to Hell 40th Anniversary Trailer - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - Highway to Hell (from Countdown, 1979) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - Highway to Hell (Live at Donington, 8/17/91) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - Dirty Deeds Done Dirt Cheap (Live at Donington, 8/17/91) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - Whole Lotta Rosie (from No Bull) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - You Shook Me All Night Long (from No Bull) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - Let There Be Rock (Official Video) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;AC/DC - Happy New Year! - Have A Drink On Me - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Static-X Official 20th Anniversary Wisconsin Death Trip World Tour PROMO - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Wisconsin Death Trip 20th Anniversary Tour - Australia - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Wisconsin Death Trip 20 Year Anniversary Tour / Static-X / Devil Driver / Dope / Wayne Memorial - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Static X Official "Project Regeneration" Teaser - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;‘Shazam' Trailer Ft. "My Name Is" - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Eminem - Good Guy (Behind The Scenes) ft. Jessie Reyez - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Eminem - Good Guy ft. Jessie Reyez - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Eminem - "Kick Off" (Freestyle) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Bodied - Official Feature Film - directed by Joseph Kahn and Produced by Eminem - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Behind the Scenes - Eminem Jimmy Kimmel Live “Venom” Performance – Presented by Google Pixel 3 - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Eminem Performs "Venom" from the Empire State Building on Jimmy Kimmel Live - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Bodied - Uncensored Official Trailer - Produced by Eminem - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Bodied - Official Trailer - Produced by Eminem. - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Eminem - Venom - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Eminem x Sway - The Kamikaze Interview (Part 4) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;KILLSHOT [Official Audio] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Eminem x Sway - The Kamikaze Interview (Part 3) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Eminem - Lucky You ft. Joyner Lucas - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Eminem x Sway - The Kamikaze Interview (Part 2) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - The Great Expanse’ World Tour Europe AND UK Part 3 - Contained GENERIC phrase: Tour.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - ‘The Great Expanse’ World Tour Europe AND UK Part 2 - Contained GENERIC phrase: Tour.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - ‘The Great Expanse’ World Tour Europe AND UK Pt. 1 - Contained GENERIC phrase: Tour.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - Brisbane Australia, Riverstage Night 2 (The Great Expanse World Tour) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Tour.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - Brisbane Australia, Riverstage Night 1 (The Great Expanse World Tour) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Tour.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - Adelaide Australia, AEC (The Great Expanse World Tour) - Contained GENERIC phrase: Tour.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - Melbourne Australia, Rod Laver Arena Round 2 (The Great Expanse World Tour) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - Melbourne Australia, Rod Laver Arena Night 1 (The Great Expanse World Tour) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - Queenstown New Zealand, July 2019 (The Great Expanse World Tour) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - Wellington New Zealand, July 2019 (The Great Expanse World Tour) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - Auckland New Zealand, July 2019 (The Great Expanse World Tour) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - Splendour In The Grass 2019 Recap - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - Bendigo Groovin the Moo Recap - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Hilltop Hoods - Townsville Groovin the Moo Recap - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Foo Fighters - Best Of You (Live At Wembley Stadium, 2008) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Foo Fighters - Ramble On (Live At Wembley Stadium, 2008) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Foo Fighters - Show Open (Live at Wembley Stadium, 2008) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Foo Fighters - Rock And Roll (Live At Wembley Stadium, 2008) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Foo Fighters - Credits (Live At Wembley Stadium, 2008) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Foo Fighters - Everlong (Live At Wembley Stadium, 2008) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Foo Fighters - Monkey Wrench (Live At Wembley Stadium, 2008) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Foo Fighters - All My Life (Live At Wembley Stadium, 2008) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Foo Fighters - My Hero (Live At Wembley Stadium, 2008) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Foo Fighters - Marigold (Live At Wembley Stadium, 2008) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Foo Fighters - Skin And Bones (Live At Wembley Stadium, 2008) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Foo Fighters - Cold Day In The Sun (Live At Wembley Stadium, 2008) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Foo Fighters - Long Road To Ruin (Live At Wembley Stadium, 2008) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Foo Fighters - Learn To Fly (Live At Wembley Stadium, 2008) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;Foo Fighters - Breakout (Live At Wembley Stadium, 2008) - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys - Detroit 'Let's Rock' Tour Poster - Contained GENERIC phrase: Tour.
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys – Eagle Birds ["Let's Rock" Tour Rehearsals] - Contained GENERIC phrase: Tour.
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys - I Got Mine ["Let's Rock" Tour Rehearsals] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys - Lonely Boy ["Let's Rock" Tour Rehearsals] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys - “Let’s Rock” Tour Promo [St. Louis #1] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys - “Let’s Rock” Tour Promo [Denver #2] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys - "Let's Rock" Voicemail #2 [1-740-303-ROCK] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys - "Let's Rock" [Promo #20] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys - "Let's Rock" [Promo #19] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys - Go ["Let's Rock" Tour Rehearsals] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;The Black Keys - "Let's Rock" Voicemail #1 [1-740-303-ROCK] - Older than 60 days.
&lt;br&gt;4LKOCOLORS by Alkopoligamia - video lookbook - Contained not followed artist.

&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
<dc:creator> &lt;a&gt;Bednar&lt;/a&gt;</dc:creator>
</item>
</rdf:RDF>